
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<articles>
<article>
,Pla2A577411TX` 
'December 'Tedium :issue, 1994 
in THIS 111011TH'S PROCRIISTInnToR 
Dr. Twilight's lecture series on the powers of unreliability and sotective Ii competence in the workplace 
Ida Vennybuddy speaks of bow to get the nuggets from your man on Christmas 
Trace the family origins of the fllud bank to their hairy. boozy. resin *lotted toots 
Journey to 5. Scott Orabbe's land of lost Adolescent Vanity and rediscover those elements of yourself that your parents abhorred for Ignored/ and your peers relished. 
Discover why none of the topics ever listed on this masthead ever appear in the Issue 

951 2nd Ave., NYC 
10022 
The quasi-monthly prodigal fanzine of the Mexican Mud Band. 
emna Altet; 
FRI DEC 23 I 1 pm MLA MU New York NY SAT DEC 31 lOpm THE fiCrIt New York NY FRI JAN 6 l limn NEW IlkIJIC arc New York NY FRI JAN 13 10prn (MKT TAVERN New Bruns. NJ FRI JAN 14 I Ipm Mal MtIJIC cArc Ncw York NY FRI JAN 27 lOpm tiODODTJ 11111 Mahwah NJ SAT JAN 28 lOpm CADAL00.5i1 New Palrz NY 
(212) 966-4225 (212)686.4863 (212) 941.0900 (908) 545-7265 (212) 941-0900 (201) 529-2357 (914) 255-3400 
Fri & Sat FF133A4 OLD CITY HALL/EAST LA. OswesciSwacume NY 
Were you abducted by an al.ro you constantly quote the Jerky Boys? Let us know, send us E-mail at Daves new address: dpa Qbfin.com Want a copy of the Mud's CD? send SI2 to MUD MERCH, 951 Second Ave, 2nd Floor, NYC 10022. Make checks payable to Mark Czuj. Want our free newsletter?: The PROCRASTINATOR CALL TNT HOUSE Or MUD a ( 2 1 2 ) 7 5 9-04 5 4 
IRK 112) 1 ni 01,V7/55 16 : 41 DeR-P. #5 akilNY 7 JAN /rgS 
David Maxwell 222 E. 17th St. #2F New York NY 10003 
bUtaMommaly 
</article>
<article>

In what can only be called the single most outrageous, blatantly uninformed statement of this century, a rival rock-band newsletter recently accused the PROCRASTINATOR — your friend and official fanzine of the Mexican Mud Band — of writing "self-obsessed, meandering, poorly structured, socially unconscionable essays that achieve nothing in the way of promotion or value." We here at the Procrastinator are deeply mortified, appalled and...wounded. Do our meaningless articles seem to 
be about nothing, or isn't being "about" nothing what "being" is all about? Otherwise what are we being, being Beings? The answer is Beings are meant to be Nothing. To be about Nothing is to be about Being. All who are being will be nothing and all that is nothing will be being. And thus to be a being writing about nothing is to circum-vent the circle, and that's like triple beaming! So there, Mr. ski-capped critic! 
These untalented fosterers of so-called "good" journalism who laugh 
at us, they are like ancient dinosaurs laughing at the first furred rodent. We would laugh at them, but, alas are too full. Instead, we may lean back in our rockers, pat the vial of sedatives at out sides, and mutter, "There's them that laugh, and there's them that knows better." 
If our lack of interesting things to say makes you mad, good. We've been encouraging work from all our readers, but no one has anything to say beyond "Dear Mud. Please put me on your newsletter mailing 
list." So, get mad and send us scathing reviews. Send us your entries and win fantastic prizes. See the Abe E. Piece Foundation Literacy Contest information listed below. See Amelia, the hamburger boy who dances the Charleston. See Elmo, the hair-lipped elm-tree with a lisp who can solve any trigonometry problem known to man! Stump him and win a big elm log to take home for your fire! Remember what Zealot McDougal says, "If you're the type who can't type, then write!!" 
WIN THE PROCRASTINATO "PIECE" PRIZE! 
"Creativity is wasted in the minds of the young, and young in the minds of the wasted." - Abe E. Piece 
In honor of the fourteenth year of the passing of our honorable "spiritual" guide, Abe E. Piece, we present the literary contest that bears his name. Abe E. was a sham shaman, but he had the obtuse mind of a profoundly long-winded and uninteresting Marxism professor, and those who man-aged to stay awake through one his harangues were often rewarded with an occasional jest or flatulence joke. He was assassinated by Lithuanian mimes in 1976, a harsh fact omitted from most high-school text-books, which still portray these anarchic street performers as gentle, misunder-stood simpletons. His dream was to upset the Paris entertainment aristoc-racy and create a new order of amusement, a world where mime was despised and irreverence and cantankerous ambivalence were the sure-fire laugh-getters of the day. In order to keep those odious mimes on the run, we at the foundation that bears his great name, are offering for the 14th consecutive year since his gruesome, lonely death, the three tier cre-ative writing contest that bears his all-but-forgotten family name, the Procrastinator "Piece" prize. 
AWARDS FOR BEST IN POETRY, SHORT FICTION and ESSAY 
ONE: POETRY. On a somewhat clean piece of paper, write a poem of moving depth and honesty on one or all of the following topics: a) Broken dreams; broken bottles; b) the unfathomably vast amount of words in the English language; c) the tragic problem of immigrant Lithuanian mimes in America circa 1980, or d) none of the above 
TWO: SHORT FICTION: In a stapled together, white mass of paper, illus-trate with pointed simplicity a saga, or if you will, mini-saga, that focuses 
on: a) The virtues inherent in decadent excess; b) The curse of a need for creative expression among suburban, up-state New York teens; c) The principle teachings of the great Abe E. Piece, namely "co-eccentricity" and "selective ineptitude" or d) any other theory of "questionable practicality". 
THREE: ESSAY: Enamorate with effortless effervescence on one of the following topics: a) Sexuality: Genetic Con or Spiritual Salvation?; b) Social Awareness: How it Can be Dimmed; c) Abe E Piece: Spiritual Healer or Drug-Addled Misanthrope? or d) Original Essay Topic: What do I know? I'm just a person!" 
Send xeroxes or original work to: The Abe E. Piece Foundation c/o Erich Kuersten / 951 2nd Ave. #1 / NYC / 10022. NOTE: Nothing will be returned without written permission from Mr. Piece's estate. (To insure safe return of manuscript, write: "Please, Abe E. Peace! Abe E., please! "— Please Abe E. Abe E. Peace, please! Please, Abe E. Peace..." over and over on the back of each submission. Allow three or more weeks for response, results, rejections, insults, grotesque facial gestures, etc.) 
PRIZES; Poetry: 1st Prize: Publication in the PROCRASTINATOR, Official Abe E. Piece Foundation award, plaque, ring, sticker, shirt and deluxe hardcover edition of "Pass the Piece: The Complete Abe E. Piece Canon of Spiritual Commentary and Incoherent Mumbling." A $99. value! Short Fiction: Publication in the PROCRASTINATOR, a late-night, very loud telephone call of congratulations from Dave Parsons, over $20 in valuable coupons, a chance to spend the weekend, all expenses paid, at the Abe E. Pierce Center for Spiritual Enlightening and Wallet Lightening; Essay: Publication in the PROCRASTINATOR and a possible position as regular contributorl In a time to be announced, you will have the opportu-nity to go head-to-head with a staff member of the PROCRASTINATOR, and you'll get first choice of weapons. If you can vanquish our staff me ber, his job is yours! No quarter! ,Y1 Deadline is midnight, New Years Eve, 1994/5. All other forms of printe ssl matter are invited to be submitted to the PROCRASTINATOR in the meantime, including comics, profane illustrations, bawdy limericks, hideously juvenile scrawls and even flowery sentiment. Don't get off yot-. „.„ butt, fellow procrastinators, but do reach for your notebook and let us share your crusted commentary. (The above was a paid announcement of the Abe E. Piece Foundation, Waukeegan, IL) 
Cut to Commercial: MUD BAND'S "NOW WITH MORE SALT!" PROVEN EFFECTIVE AGAINST GASTRITIS! 
One out of ten Doctors recommend regular listenings of the Mexican Mud Band's latest, Now With More Salt, " the "choice" compact disc that all moms say is unbeatable for smooth, gentle relief. Ahh, relief. Relief of annoying silence, relief of peaceful contemplation, not to mention general coherence. 
(NOTE: C.D. contains no actual salt or salt residue) 
2 Procrastinator • December, 1992 
