
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<articles>
<article>
CE-1271117 
9thl /14ilows (Zeigh610/4/0 Level 
This month we bring you the greasy pan drippings of New York City least reliable journalists: - Follow Erich down a meandering path of tedious sell-references! - Find out why Ida finds it hard to love! - Discover the mystery of Dave Parsons cereal fetish! - Jhudder with revulsion at Max s darkest confes-sion! - Enjoy our new party snacks! - cringe, wine and parry at the razor wit of Baklava eater Achmed airman! 
/0 Wait me WI un worn min nut int en so' 
 salPannensuce a Cot 
11 &ACM 11 i ribr liS 
,SAT. NOV 26 • 10pm • New Music Cure Kew Ybrk (212)'9at !Sr 
FRI DEC 2 I 1pm New Music Cafe New York NY i 212i 941-1005 
SAT DEC 3.l( us Globe Theater Norwalk Cr (203) 866-2999  
SAT DEC 10 10pm Nobody's Inn Mahwah NJ (201) 529-2357 
THU DEC IS lOpm Stanhope (louse Stanhope NJ ( 201) 347-0458 
FRI DEC 16 I Iprn New Music Cafe New York NY (212)941-1008  
SAT DEC 17 I mu Cab. 1 Bin Ithaca NY 
1I 
SAT DEC 31 10pm The Acme New York NY (212) 686-4863 
If you could likc to attend our New Year's Extra% aganta it the Acme III NYC please contact Donna ir. (212) 686-4863. Tickets arc limited, so don't delay. Call now and ■ou nil' also =eke this hand' set of steak knit es. FREE OF CHARGE I tifiti pr hen/ whisvunwkehk• Want a copy of the Mud's CD? send $12 to 951 2nd Ave. 2nd FL NYC 10022 Make checks payable to Mark Cluj Want info or more stuff!?? CALI (or warn') THE wousr Or t4111D @ (212) 759-0454 

951 2nd Ave., 2nd floor, NYC 10022 
David Maxwell 222 E. 17th M2F New York NY 10003 
a' PM 
:5 NOV /9 9 A 
</article>
<article>
You Suck! 
Don't get mad at me when I tell you this.it's the truth! We all suck, whether through a straw, or on a lozenge, or down an ice cold beer. There is nothing wrong with "sucking" In this manner, and yet the word sucking is such a neg-ative one, popularized to a ridiculous extreme by Beavis and Butthead, that a young person is bound to be besieged by self-doubt when embarking upon a round of "sucking". After all, no one sucks more than babies, on a pacifier or bottle or nipple, and surely they are not to be shunned or ridiculed for this?! 
The worst is that with Beavis and Butthead's popularity, the square older marketers of the world are adopting the negative connotation of "suck" to relate to the world's youth. "Suck" Is used everywhere as a catch phrase to help tap Into their baby wallets. A typical commercial might read "Try our gum, the one that doesn't suck" orSchool sure sucks, but not when you're on a sugar high like the one you get from Slug Barr Why is sucking such a stig-ma? 
Of course, we all know it is the orally sexual connotation of the world that makes it so despicable. Yet, wouldn't it seem a little stupid of Beavis and Butthead, two pathetic virgins, to shun this act with such cavalier brazen-ness? Sucking is associated with a sexual act that is very specialized among humans. It Is done to men by their lovers and it causes them great ecstasy, and yet, there is no reward, no lofty position granted to the generous lover who performs this sucking action. In fact, "Yo, suck my d----" Is considered an incredible insult. Shouldn't it serve as the impassioned request of a loved one? I am sure there is nothing any self-respecting hedonist male would like more than to have this action performed on them, and yet they stigmatize the word In layer upon layer of insidiously vile adolescent significance. 
So, let's get together and think about sucking in a more positive light, boys and girls. And the next time someone tells you that you suck, smile and say "Thank you. Not only that, but I suck with Intensity!" 
MAN IN CLEVELAND REVEALS LACK OF INTEREST IN OJ CASE 
His neighbors little suspected. His wife, who watched court TV avidly, had no clue. Then, last night, Edward Pinque dropped his paper In his lap, finished his third manhattan and defiantly declared that he had no interest whatsoever In the OJ mse."I still can't believe this is true." his wife said in a soh-ridden statement to the press. "He always seemed Interested, even during the sec-ond hour of that Bronco police chase." 
The national press Is trying to discredit Mr. Pinque, calling him everything from "hopelessly Jaded by an overwhelming amount of media stimuli" to "moron" in the desperate hopes that nobody In America will realize that somebody else shares their lack of fascination with what is bing called the murder trial of the century. Mr. Pinque, when asked to comment on what sort of backlash his apathetic stance might create, could only spit, shrug and admit that he didn't care about that either. Good going, Pinquel 

Pinque: Bigger fish to fry? 
2 
O Procrastinator's GUIDE T FALL 
Garth Flurrybush reports FASHION, 1994 
Of course by now every one In the fashion world Is livid over Anthony Spaglioni's plan to unveil a new line of sleeved sleeveless flannel shirts, part of his gigantic "Dumb Beaux" Ilne that will feature surface pattern design only on the Inside of the garment. "Completely invisi-ble to the naked eye," Spaglioni hinted to me during an especially perfumy summer yachting accident. "You have to turn them inside out to see the patterns. On the outside, they look.." he paused for a heightened sense of fopperic drama, "...like crap." Already there is a fervent bidding war over Spaglioni's new line. Apparently many other top designers are concerned that the fine is so awful that It might in fact end the world of high fashion as we know it, creat-ing a sort of apocalypse of haute couture, so there is a furious furor to buy Spaglioni out and make sure the c'ethes never reach the states. 
"This line of clothing is so embarrassing and awful,' commented fashion scholar Eunice Malidegh, "that It can't he but catch on among the young Americans here." Grunge Is the height of twenties Parisian fashion compared with Mr. Spaglionl's so called "Dumb-Beaux" !line. 
SLACKER'S GUIDE TO CHEAP FALL VIDEO BUYS 
Procrastinating without a videotape library is almost a complete waste of time. To just aim-lessly channel-surf off cable is stupefying, and a good procrastinator doesn't need to be any stupider. Therefore a large personal library of tapes is necessary so that the next late-night vkleofest you run can remain free of the "psychic-home-network" or "Nightllne". If you go and try to buy a pre-recorded video-tape, they can be expensive. You can make your own tapes off cable, but who can remember when the movies are on? Unless you have two VCRs It's impossible to tape tapes (even with two, copyguards are everywhere). For some of us hardcore slackers, this Is just too much damn effort. The following is a Ilst of some great movies that you are likely to find in the "bargain bin" of any major chain, I.e.: Tower, Wiz, etc. shuffled amidst the "Golfer's Weakest Practical Bloopers Vol VII," and 'Monster Truck Expo Meets the Shao-Un Destroyer" for about $1 to $4.99 each. 
1. Carnival of Souls (Average retail: $5) 1962, Dlr. Herk Harvey An eerie black and white masterpiece about a non-religious church organist who finds her-self caught between life and death, stuck in the relentlessly empty world of middle America woman, haunted by nightmares that bleed Into daily life. The lead, Candice Hikfigloss, gives a classic performance, tut the main credits belong to the cast of characters that sur-round her as she tries to adjust to life, the demon pursuing her seems showy and normal in comparison to their genuine normality which is the creepiest thing in the film. An absolute must-own at the price 
2. Joe (available now at the bargain rack by your local Wiz cashier: $3.99) 1970 Peter Boyle (In a pre-"Young Frankenstein" role) is a lower-class hippie-hating bigot who befriends an upper-class hippie-killer (who murdered his daughter's drug-dealing beaux) The two demented dads go "undercover and wind up in bed with two free-lovin' women, but when these drugged-out wantons reveal they prefer their snotty young moocher male companions for the long-term, they get mad and start shooting. This Is a movie you'll want to show again and again to your friends. 
3. Creature from the Haunted Sea (Average retail: $5) and The Little Shop of Horrors, (Dlr. Roger Gorman) In this period of the fifties, schlock-master Roger Corman was adopt-ing a sort of a like "beatnik" feel to his horror movies In order to hit two markets at once for the then thriving drive-Ins of middle America as well as the hipper "grindhouses" of Times Square. Murder and crazy existential dialogue flow throughout both, "it's like hep, man." 
Procrastinator Disclaimer: 
Publisher is not liable for decrease in quality of material and reserves the right to blame aforementioned decrease on Acts of God, action by any government or quasi-governmen-tal entity, fire, flood, Insurrection, riot, explosion, embargo, strikes-whether legal or Mega!, labor or material shortage, transportation interruption of any kind, work slowdown, pro-longed sobriety, lack of staff interest, failure on part of readers to provide feedback, para-noia, air or sea attack by Roden, Mothra, hangover, head lice, field mice, and/or fried rice. Thank you 
Procrastinator • November, 1994 


Max's 3FRIAL Quiz 
1. What was the piece of evi- b: spongy dence that finally got Ted Bundy c: slimy the chair? d: like Denny's chicken fried a: fingerprints on aerosol can steak b: bite marks In Lisa Levy's but-tocks 7. How many times did Charlie c: fibers from Bundy's sweater Starkweather stab his girlfriend's found on sorority =pet father? Her mother? Her 2-year-old sister? 2. How many skulls were found in Jeffrey Dahmer's apartment ? 8. How many needles did X-rays What color were they painted? reveal Imbedded In cannibal a: Six. Grey Alfred Fish's groin (which almost b: Four. Red short-cIrcuited the electric c: Ten. Purple chair)? d: Eight. Paisley a. 14 b. 37 3: The nickname that little c. 172 Charlie Manson's mommy gave d. 216 him. A good sign of the quality nurturing she provided 9. Although a lot of self-ordained a. Little Squirmy serial killer "experts"consider b. Mister Hothead him to be the greatest mass c. Bitey murderer, this psychedelic d. No•name Maddox prophet never actually killed anyone. 4. What part of the victims did 10. The method of ligature by Arthur Shawcross. the Genesee which Albert DeSalvo, the River Killer devour? Boston Strangler, dispatched of a: liver his 13 victims. b: legs a. hands c: buttocks b. rope d: genitalia c. tie 5. How many demonic voices did d. his estranged wife Valerie's David Berkowitz hear In his favorite scarf. head? What are their names? 11. This country provides a cozy 6. When Jeffrey Dahmer ate a home to 98% of the serial killers victim's liver It tasted: ever reported In the annals of a: rubbery criminal history. ivsn A0 pope 'Lt. Loseci ro wino P'4 P'01. eta pus seitael-IM uosuun sepeq0 '6 uqof 'ietsuoirq p 'e P'8 porn eqt '(roxof 13 •z 99 '91. 'Z1. 'L ettI) umber `oulso0 q • L q -9 )loaf` iereuee • 9'9 MOMSUV And now the obligatory esoteric  MATCHING GAME instructions; Match the Mud member or A. Dave B. Marc C. Matt D. Scott E. Don F. Erich G. Max H. Darren Procrastinator staff contributor to the right with their dominant characteristics listed below. 1. Obdurate-a:hardened In feelings b:stubbomiy persistent in wrongdoing 2. Vociferous-so loud or insistent as to draw atten-tion 3. Laconic-using or Involving a minimum of words 4. Obstreperous-marked by unruly or aggressive noisiness. See vociferous 5. Lugubrious-exaggeratedly or affectedly mournful 6. impecunious-having little or no money usu. habitually 7. PolemicaUDIspulatious-given to aggressive attacks on or refutations of the principals and philosophies of another 8. Vituperative-having a tendency to make unqual-ified/capricious judgments and critidsms 9. Dilatory- characterized by procrastination 10. Pertinacious-Adhering resolutely to an opin-ion, purpose or design; perversely persistent. 11. Euglenoid - typically green or colorless stigma- bearing solitary organisms with one or two flagella emerging from a well defined gullet. 12. Parsimonious - frugal to the point of stinginess 
COMIC WITH THANKSGIVING 
Your Guide to Familial Evaluation and Ice-Cube Rationing. 
In the following test you will learn to evaluate your relationship with your family, your mate's family (if you have one), and your tolerance for alcohol. From this knowledge you will learn how to relate to your relations, feel warmth when warmth is called for, and most importantly, to learn how to drink Just enough to enjoy yourself this Thanksgiving. 
PART ONE: THE TOLERANCE TEST (This test will take 4 1/2 hours). 
Sample Question: How are you? 
a. Awesome! b. Sucky. c. Never better, sir. 
(Correct answer d) 
You have until the pre-game show is over to answer the following questions: 
1. My neighbor, Emmanuel, bought a sheepdog. Ever since there's been white hair In my rose-bushes. My wife thinks I'm crazy. Do you see that fur there, no...there?" 
a. The hair is there, Mr. Antlglione, it's the hair of my ancestors, of death, and of rebirth, it's the hair of ancient witches who are like mothers to life Itself, they are like doves in the wake of the flood. Shun not this dog-hair, Mr. Antiglione, it makes your roses grow. b. Emmanuel? What Is he? A 1-in Haitian? You say the word dad, and I'll ice that dog. c. I don't see anything, I think I hear your wife calling you." d. All of the above. 
2. So, what can I get YOU to drink? 
a. Uh, whatever b. What have you got? c. nothing, thank you. d. beer. 
3. If you answered "b" go on to this question, If not, skip to question 31. What will you have? Perrier? Coke? Beer? 
a. Perrier sounds dandy b. What kind of beer? c. Do you got something the Coke could chase? d. What else you got? 
4. Why, There might be some Ouzo left from last New Years. Snuggle-Axe, Where's that Ten-High bourbon we got from the christmas party? if you'd prefer beer, there's Moison and Genny Light in the cooler. 
a. I don't know what Ouzo is, but tell Snuggle-Axe to find it quick. b. Ten high, ten high, ten high. c. I can't believe you're really intending to serve me alcohol. d. I think it's passing out Urns. 
5. After locating a secret stash of Dom Perignon, you vomit on the family carpet. Your best move now would be to: 
a. Urinate on yourself b. Declare your love for Fable openly to all who listen. • HIt your mom up for money d. Embark upon a career as a solo folksinger 
6-12. 1n a heated after-dinner discussion, the topic turns to religion. Match the following alcohol Intake combinations with the proper level of dogmatic zeal In the ensuing argument: 
COCKTAIL DINNER DRINK RELIGIOUS STANCE 
a. 1 beer 2 wines 6. Indignantly Satanic b. 3 gin and tonics 3 gins 7. Holier-than-thou sober c. diet coke 1 wine 8. Smugly pseudo-Buddhist d. 3 beers seltzer 9. self-righteously Socratic e. 4 highballs alioa-seltzer 10. gloriously drunk 1. 1 beer half a beer 11. violently non-Catholic g. 6 ouzos beer-seltzer 12. silent during entire conversation 
13. The Cowboys are suffering badly at the hands of the Rams. If Grandpa asks you If you think the Cowboys can make a comeback during the third quarter, and you don't really care, you're best bet to still escape from having to talk to him Is: a. Ignore him completely b. Feign Interest until your sober enough to leave the table c- Promise him a certain Cowboy victory, and then steal his wallet. d. Run away In tears 
Procrastinator • November, 1994 3 


WAR OF THE WORLDS WON! PIESE"IFOS ARE A:ONG VS!"  
the government officially admitted to a cover-up today, one spanning over 40 years and involv-ing cattle mutilations, crop circles, UFOs and. embarrassingly enough, Elvis sightings. The president revealed in a short-speech to an stunned press that the top levels of the US govern-ment have been taking drastic measures to keep alien visitation a secret, employing such under-handed means as discrediting witnesses, confiscating extra-terrestrial evidence and dancing around making loud donkey noises to distract attention. "Until now, policy has been to keep Joe Average American a tranquil and assured consumer, free to watch banal TV, indulge in delusions of grandeur and consume conspicuous amounts of beef and milk products," the presi-dent said. "I'm here to say, Mr. Joe Average American, those salad days are done. Dinner it served!" The president then went on to announce that the government will work to educate the people by signing a deal with Amco Entertainment and HBO to produce a startlingly long mini-series dealing with the 40-year conspiracy. It will be called "Plan Ten" and star Parker Louis Stevenson, Elke Sommer and Don Knotts. Rumor has it that Mr. T has been approached about playing the Reverend AI Sharpton, (who although in no way involved in the cover-up, is insist-ing he be included). 
ALIENS LAUNCH "STAR" INTO AMERICAN HOMES! 
Among the scheduled highlights of the mini-series will be "Enis", an EBE (Extraterrestrial Biologic Entity is the government's term for our little green visitors) who is apparently the hottest thing going in the rest of the TV watching galaxy. Enis is currently making plans to visit Earth as the first official "superstar" from another world. "Mork, My Favorite Martian, E.T., they are all so meager! Now you have me, Enis! You will buy many products with my face on them, and will look foolish no morel" Euis will be the first alien super-pop-star who is at the same time not a transvestite. Enis resembles if anything a cross between the creature in Close Encounters (whose director he is planning to sue for royalties in the near future) and a pint-sized New York real estate broker. 
"On my planet, we have no water," lamented Enis at a press conference to announce the series. "You will see just how thirsty I am during the premiere. I must drink several times a year. And I cannot urinate, for we aliens do not have pissing-tools, obviously since on our planet there is no water." Even after explaining this phenomenon several times, few scientists would believe him. Many noteworthy scientist are still unwilling to believe in the aliens at all, including renowned sky-watcher Karl Sagan who feels there is ;to evidence beyond what our five senses can gasp to indicate they actually exist_ The truth will be corning soon, as Enis already has plans to "bare" all, as we'll soon discover when, this November, when he will pose nude for a spread in the American Journal of Science. 
MEXICAN MUD ALMOST BURNS TO DEATH IN SYRACUSE ARE 
East L.A., Syracuse NY Enrico Suave reports, Thousands were packed into a sweaty horde of nervousness, soon to be denied what they had dreamt of from the start, what? 
let's try that again MUD MEMBERS CHARGED WITH OBNOXIOUSNESS. LENITY, DISTURBANtE., 
Oswego, New York Ericho Guave reports: Scott "the Musician" Lehr and Don "1G-ions" Martin were recently sentenced to over tour hours weak labor last Saturday when, follow-ing a raucous out-of-town gig, they were discovered during a routine police frisk to be car-rying well over $5 in mini-soaps and shampoos stolen from a Quality Inn, from which they had recently checked out. A frightened maid soon stepped forward to charge them with smart alecky comments, pseudo-Marx-Brotherish antics and atrocious grooming habits. Also implicated, though still at large, is the notorious Dave "The Instigator" Parsons, who apparently ordered a single room at the hotel, knowing full well that over 40 people were planning on sleeping there. "I ask him how many people," said Achmed Amann, the night-clerk, "and he said 'one' meaning him. Then I walk past room, there is laughter, many people laughing, door opens, I look in. I realize he lie! This Dave Smith, he a liar! Not one people like he say! So many people, on tloor, on bed, and toilet paper...people and toilet paper everywhere!" 
Apparently the Mud were playing "toilet-paper baseball," a game where toilet paper rolls are substituted for balls, a lamp often serves as a bat, and the bases are "anywhere broken glass isn't." Since a storage closet had been left open down the hall, there was no shortage of balls, and within hours the room was thigh-deep in tissue. When asked who won, a young woman who was at the scene could only guess, "I think the loud, drunken fat guy won." 
Don "the Dean of Mean" Martin, due to his parents being in closest proximity, was the first to be freed on the $20 bail, immediately he was re-arrested for lewdness. Apparently, Mr. Martin exited the holding tank "hanging brain", a crime against good-taste which car-ries a very stiff penalty in the colder towns pt upstate New York. The courageous dangler commented later that he was unrepentant over his small deed; admitting he was, in fact, looking forward to some quality jail time, since he now has a roommate to watch his dog back home in NYC. He currently faces well over three hours in cengresstonai red tape. So with Don cheerfully awaiting life imprisonment, Scott still anxiously hoping for his dad's promised fed-exed check, and P.P. Parsons still at large, hunted and despised, we are left with only Mark "Shangley Man" Czuj and Matt "Own" Pedone free from charges, we can only wonder how this courageous band will get home in time for the new Simpson, 
Classlessifieds 
Your guide to the obtuse, the frustrated and the vapid 
MISCELLANEOUS TEXT  etc.crawis like a belly on upside down parade, that dances to the ministry, a thousand forgotten shades of violet and violence, ultra-blue, of thieves and ply-goods, of dry-woods. Dances farther than a belly, up and down and backwards....  PERSONALS  SWMGF seeks same emotional and epoxy-related bond. I like dining out and eating In (and know how to do 
4 
PERSONALS  them both simultaneously) don't wait! Xavier Temps: 334-9087 
EMPLOYMENT  ACTORS/ACTRESSES: If you're not afraid of the $SS  that you could be making right now instead of your cur-rent, paltry, meager pay, or if you just want the undivided attention of the world, give us a call - No gimmicks! Our organization is looking for YOU, If you're (a) an attractive woman with no 
EMPLOYMENT  moral reserves about getting what you want or (b) an even more attrac-tive woman who Is comfortable with 'adult' environments. Men may feel free to apply, and are welcome to wile away the hours in our reception area until they get the message. Call Anthony - 1-900 334-9009  LAZY WHITE BOYS are anxious to waste your money! Call 976-SLACK to cite New fork's most shiftless temps! Equal Opportunist Employer. 
'DID SOMEONE silly RPicl Ng Boist)? ,JO;N US FOR NEW YEARS call (212) 686-4863 
Procrastinator • November, 1994 

