
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<articles>
<article>
THE PRONNITINIITOR 
INSIDE! - A MEANINGLESS MUD trrERvmw! - YUMMY SOUP FROM MEASY S HEADSTRONG? 
- ENDLESS LAUGHS FROM DOOM SPONGOFTEN? 
SPFCTAL molcovER ysstrE 
ALL Ti4E JUICY BABBLE FOR YOUR TORTURED SUNDAY AFTERNOON READNG1 No more will a soggy brain and a listless body interrupt your raging cycle. crow' those who know hangovers as a daily struggle, you can now learn how to live with your voracious thirst peacefully. --- 
111■11.11 

MrnalL0* AtACID/210)11% 
THU MAR 3 lOpm Desmond's Tavern New York, NY (212) 685.0901 SAT MAR 5 Ilpm The Lion's Den Greenfield. MA (212) 477.2782 THU MAR 10 10pm Desmond's Tavern New York, NY (212) 685-0901 FRI MAR 11 lOpm West Side Cheers Binghampton, NY (607) 723.3205 SAT MAR 12 1pm SUNY Bingham pton Live TV 61 Radio Simulcast Concert WED MAR 16 9pm The Nines Ithaca, NY (212) 229-2122 THU MAR 17 9pm Filthy McNasry's Seneca Falls, NY (315) 568-2323 FRI MAR 18 10pm East L.A. Syracuse, NY (315) 471.1148 SAT MAR 19 10pm Old City Hall Oswego, NY (315) 343.2012 MON MAR 21 10pm Nightingales New York, NY (212) 473.9398 THU MAR 24 10pm Desmond's Tavern New York, NY (212) 685.0901 FRI MAR 25 9pm The Hotel Rhinecliff Rhinecliff, NY (914) 876-8688 MON MAR 26 lOpm The Court Tavern New Brunswick, N) (908) 545.7265 THU MAR 31 lOpm The Cabaret Ardmore, PA (215) 688.4600 FRI APR 1 9pm Images Suffern, NY MON APR 4 9pm The Jukebox Long Island, NY THU APR 7 lOpm Desmond's Tavern New York, NY (212) 685.0901 FRI APR 8 I ipm Ludlow Scree( Cafe New York, NY (212) 353.0536 SAT APR 9 10pm Star Cantina Rhinestone, NY (914) 876.8616 

<(51 As,c ^a N'1 0022 
Within: The inevitable rehash of American mothers' most feared journalism! 
</article>
<article>
117 THE MED HEWS! 
ARE MURDERER NOW AN FDA-APPROVED BREAKFAST CEREAL!!! 
A warning to all consumers. Mr. Al Kellyue. convicted axe-wielder. has just won FDA consumer approval and as of March 31st will be considered • mandatory Ingredient in all breakfast cereal made in the U.S. 
'We have done two tests,• explained • withered FDA spokesperson, and so far, nobody's been axed to death as a result.' Though those two tests were done with mice. who are unable to wield axes. the FDA official (who asked that his name be witheldl swore that he could see only benefits 
to mankind In the long run.' by suffusing America's favorite breakfast with the mutant DNA strains of a psychopath. 'les not even like Al IS • genius.' noted Al's old cell-mate. Scott Lehr. 'I mean he ain't no Hannibal Lechter. Why suffuse our bodies with the DNA of • dumb psychopath?' When asked if there was any rational reason why this was happening, the FDA official responded: At this time. we cannot comment brother. Let me lust dose by saying. eating psycho is eating... the FUTUlkEr 
EDITOR/A1 DEPARTMENT 
Welcome back. oh siotsples of lethargy! First. please accept our hearty spologre. for the gargantuan Lapse an mu Ji•ributann ram. We only hope that the morsels wothut ate use enough to appease yaw lath of slack knowledge. Erich and I have been traveling the world in search of a truly sedentary culture to provide a mental futon for our undermsked and overpast mauls. (Actually. se rust plumb forgot to writs.) As a diwlaimen Erich has offered to bur ant disgruntled readers a few shots of Old Williamsburg Bourbon upon request. hit don't mention my name when you ask. MAX 

TELEx •1-3: *loon or Zane? 
ten the lisle went Ike Mille levet swain., Ms span lay skim on the anneal San .:estr. fans shipped a kaalorao. alined the plan oaf dwatt rm. nrIppwl all m Pars and hid la the lee all Men bad pee in a Ite•e, aerialist Islet., In ket make IIH a rabid make. Oka a mak. ukase liras wet alone ben. B saeke behest lass were dapple. loan. 
1111 /be kit-list with a ash n arcs. to tiles dads heed lad saes ao pale. lave as dep. kit. eel eel latl asleep end bid Is Mr shit an bee dept Is MIN Item tim b1010. Dna a hi woad ellinfead lines III-11st het /I calf. ranee a alai and pant the pint bleak rid blab la ant Ian. 
Nat bee phi Nark and black the KW 
tau the decd. salsa Men Ire cad rich ell it a claw. cello ad. to II earth. hat Di Bald Inc! MUHL 0 reggae hearse when shackles's banes make the seen lids senates with Ike seeds el this watered. below leads. Wilk she snack aid den,-snock el lieu cobwebbed. hairless heads. Lan a seal caked la ell. wrapped dna skki ...Pad la a roues senate It Is. tassel. kin .1111 bee seal Is seated all os the senate eel elate. Bad all the Ilikt of Nu left WI shine dews is X. trees./ In canal fell Oat soar se astral h. Y Ma It. tug IL 
in nee. a gave with two lases in IL rad   eras Iv Ikea hi anion. 
Ca the sal <same al astral sign. de 
ire assorts tree a, wen 
INTERVIEW WITH THE MEXICAN MUD 
E: So how did you glossa your wan? 
Erieb, you know how we got our stun. You were in the band. then. 
E What bead? 11 Our band, the Mexican Mud Band. E: Who are then, S: That's us. man. 
A'eorr heard olden. The cooly band was in wax... the 14watt 
0: That was way. way back. Don't tou remember we 
changed our name soph-omore rear: That ,a•ar az, /aright with •isunts Ina ine. 
I know. but we changed the name! (taught with ritual. n: Anyway. you still play with Mas in a harsh-ailed Won." E: Oh. 0: First we were the Vi}1136. Fint....timab...ate the ben, I Wok.. (etc.) 
WAYMOm,./BAYSIAVIN/7/0011///// 1/////,e5 
Sams 

TRACY at NaTra COozama comm. 
'When you wake up in the morning with your head on the and your eyes too bloody to see. you can cry in your coffee but dont call me fin asleep' What goes up must come down girls and few things re so high and fall*, teed m 8 good solid alcohol buzz My strategy to deal with hangovers involves fast treatIng the symptoms (Advil for headaches mansions for nausea. and sex if the only thing to help is to take your mind off your suBermg) Sireichmg ma good Idea ten as are Woody Allen movies espeelab Stardust Memories and Play It Again Sam I know you're not supposed to. but eating a 
0la 
4 ounce s pork rindremoved 2 MN:spoons unsalted butler 4 doves ger& Indy minced ?carrots peeko' end A-ea' 1 oruon peak/ end diced 
2zucrlund dined 1 Idaho potato peek.: tend diced 4arps, I— sect ceatnnectbroth crhorn 'merle bee! stock or 
I kme 0con whok peeko' tometoes 5 tablespoons tr-ab persky 2 teAspoons dned oregano IL? !tag:vans drerd heed SettDenapoon ground bkci pepper to taste I mare d bedneybeensorpniobeens 10 cup smell peak (smell bows or dash, Freddy grated pannesen cheese lanai= duipees 1 Cook the salt pork in a large soup pot over low heat to render theta about 10 minutes Do not let tt brown Add the butter. and when it has melted add the nark. 
carrots onion and leek and raise the heal sbghtly. Cover and wilt the vegetables for 10 minutes. sthring occasionally 2 Add the zucchini potato. both godsend tomatoes Bring to a boil Reduce the heat and add 2 tablespoons of the parsley. oregano. basil pepper. and salt Simmer over medium heat for 30 minute: 3 Add the beans tomatoes and pasta Simmer until the pasta ts tender. 10 minutes Admst the seasonings and heat through. Remove salt ork. Stir in the remammg and some with Parmesan alongiade 
SERVES 6 TO 8 ?MONS 4:1 r 4 to 6 bungorer goners, 
Frocr•sionstor • Match. 1994 
</article>
<article>
DOCTOR TWILIG5T TALKS 5ANGOVERO 
as trwr ir*firr, 9 414.4004. if relnuititft ft mans tsswentt rn 'wolf way avelaawfirn fiw+ 9 ineyniit ft raiiertf, Levee itawsrvere 44.4 * 44,44411,1 441 in 4•1 &fr. vga fir freenvialA +t +, arite LVffereafiwie kfween fir 1,444414,4 Farr. rf taasrvere Live 4Yrf I*12 4ratwered, ft,- .4 . ,affen,,+, 4rwre+m+ frr, de Live ism wide f, 4rekr arfres we. ft* Dru-frr. 
1. T-14£ "54fOULPVE 4-taP P'9 N:ER"4faNgOVER -rive rnt whikety reitki444 +swine. fie nut rf arWoe r.iL4a 444117 trwr Fries rryr eiltfyrn;stf :vows-rear& 4.s1.4kwA rff"trr firnt rustf 4t. 4rwr wnenfoerteL we(( reefed, rerAnfit. fret *reify Awn* *re 4474441146 444 rfferiwi fir awl tyr. J*eseresti*fer titeh. 1_4ter. 'wove ;errwise,prwreeff. 4441, swl frr ALI% }fru. never et., rink five iwore4via8 alcsitri nnto arw +tint yrwr 4+0,44,44 WY. art rail. rf 4aL nY.GLYef Jew+ awfrvenfe. (4.44+ 4 .1...s•4iun d*rtre con St...kernel, remind 11*.f, 4.rw .. fie eat env.. Genie ynnt 4erwn, rrwni. *Sec& errukift fir Wort+ ra4wfwf rf fie( 64.16IVIra, ii is erre*intfw frsvefralfitib eree.vev nrien wrivr moan Uzi Yf *nal. Live moat tun wrild. 
riff CURE: SeCfar iwffer. Tie Siaerrow. *We eva4 iZVOSA: Crffee, **r *s-nnrroing.. iraweiett Arm, 
2. T.ftE "SftOULIDN'TVE M9XED" 440.4410VER 9+:, L.41. 441 lavff, ft. 6..f- drink srs &Awry- ni,stf. Iff svf if Ira, .0,, 15,11.T M frr frrwde.Unndfl, arw sintf okra* 4r4vfaite, Live ariwe Linter. +Led Offer-Linnet. An:4r, +tin As+. rf Rwviefraevwfz end gtL tnrnra-nrit44- tee, trw rrsr f Tie 1.4.4ra-re i. aturwr rrwsifw 
Procestuirvator *March, 1994 
errrri-Vrmiefe fr fir nwroPer rf lair& rwk 4444 if fit inorterr in ewer leer •apre. Thaw, aorril deVotkivit fivvewr 1Voleflb inn:214.+4ff Mern.1.4 wine. Pr Inv f rffrw? fly 4.n4 Lint * sf*ra rf waft,. a* env env,* root firetirfit lafferem+ 1441. if iivvrr. avoid f4fe-n11114 air+. rf tfrine atwewre fiif inynkin rwf-rf-fnnurr frt. ft. c-rere4 Inv infr ft. red. Tit* .rein nsYkrfan rf ftia ru.-41*.dur ivawskree it 4 rrwwliws etaul**te inviretiponf wrse fr 4441eense regret. in.sstr ftdps tow ft. filth tier 4.11,441. 
7-,4E CURE: Mint, orffre, wwfer, fruit, Sir, III 
aV099: few. www4, rreratetras, ire41.441. um( 3. T3£ "9V£ 'SEEN PRUNK TOR -r +fOURS" +taNcjaVER 114 it fie ewe Isw Arad it rerwd rf, ieepaaver endwrawca 441 r447/16. 9/14 rri/.4at' it4i1 4 Ge-r/41in 4444er 4.4 Laal dortdy. Yrn. wen+ .fir 4,4an, nut in lie (oft efhr.rrn rf fie ne71. 441 wenv fee 4144Pritki„ invf if a as+ 4e i*d orwei re4ern? bfiti wrefed! 0/ five e42 rf fie Lot Inn red iawAnrer aril( f4ke slew wrkb, Inv **1- .e.4 Ti-t£ CURE: Sariawewas, Ctiirts is fit ma, wan dortre. iteVOS: SI-4/Vad Vaeiqte *ad iwrIPiiwg ref vafrrat rf fir TV *V "  q. Ti+E '9VE fEEN PRUNK **OR -r+tizEr Days-44anlovER 
tinw trwk rone1.4 Vat+, fit ow:4mr wrf-Frr. itrre r444144 Vat read eftefe 
cristal 6rf tkla ,+4t.+541-4r2.15 lywf .***71. ft reile sr ft* L,14n4e. Mny K4441 *4 I/VAT nr ernser *dr ft sprit. ifrivr Tee ire fref rrL. qtr.+ tr44n11,, prwnot tower Awe( fae * ta-nsr.r.v **.T ref,. 114 derr. Kit41 Lee ..$1/14 Live nr *owe rf fi4re. r3.5, /r4 Ivarsr Ve +14f wrw *re ly*** rwi rn +Le 64ftrrn* f(rrr eve a-44 wt. fr itiOreeins wenvr wise, iwf low Gint +WYK 41111/42 ft. HT 444. 1-44E CURE: 44rwte 4ledeni4s. .c.rahatt onnsint awn CA, 4 Ws Aintree, difirn, iniurivericfirn, rritle. fm1441. cinenv* 4,a tin;aine. 
Gl VOSP: "lonT tree, tir*44 rerivnt„ ir*renft, rent.er CD,, WM, HT, ?4 .L i*nrirer i4 fake vrtuint *iitt.(01.0.4me tnisrver Woes. twrf enrfter. Rrenenier: flow 44.t af be amfeal .94enfiefly ftei.r vrwearra,kii.&,, nut eflikt Pr., I fel-irmsrvere v+awvr rwf rwr rt4 4 rf ni.ut urn! 64 niutins awn +14+ rah aliwur, real trydniff, , i.eL drag-ariy exkwiref. Yrwtt 1,r 4 4reLik ft. rwr 1,142.t, f .nry ex/rake fttm Avowal WA/ Raval evens kr r , .1711( keen fie at4ris4 aerviws Iterwit wrw. -r-ng in2 waif • kih Offer tfwwite Iran. Lefree trw sr fr. deer, ft 'kg?. Worn- fie ClAvvrr rn fikrwsi t.rwr eirw*ap, imaiva rf h‘ffil fief, f"fmfil ile t.42 viva .tike wr {dins CVIve fir Cia.tere ter ken ft4rcLi441 firrws& lrwr Li, riin .1-roof 41.1.4 1-444 rf elf, never 6+ a. ismbsver *nun*, Inv r Lint. 41,14444 41, +114 JA/rn Rranuitrs rail: 'Tr be Lrunik is -Fr h •1161444, fr kinnk na fwc-tYns Link" Ttint *invf ef.4.4 24 Wok wr..avi,ela. 
3 
</article>
<article>
MAX'," HANGOVER POLL 
As we all know. the degree of severity a hangover takes depends not only upon the amount and types of liquor that one has drunk. but also upon one's intestinal fortitude. mental dexterity. and amount of practice with home remedies. Here are a few samples taken from interviews with a few people of renowned consumption' "Whet do you take to lessen the pain of a hangover?" 

'Hair •( the deg! Any dog!' Mar, bitter to the end 
"Sleep and cheese.' Beth, reedy (er mere 

'Anything mires with Vodka.' Joan Tesetero, fashionable addict 
'Why, cchaddya got?" Erich Karmen, near end 
'Lets of Dope.' joke [agrees., stoned again 
"Guns and money.' Da✓s Parsons,n•t to be outdone 
MUD MERCHANDISE .STICKERS-FREE!! THE CD NOW WITH MORE SALT IS FINALLY AVAILABLE!! GET YOURS TODAY!! Only $12.0011 T-SHIRTS-$10: Long/short sleeve colors, white, smears, etc. write for custom orders and limited edition 'Get Sloopid' smears and recieee your free Mexican Mud merchandise catalog. TN! MUD MERCHANT 160 1127th Street #61 NYC 10016 
Down in the Home 

4 
Procrastinator• March, 1994 
</article>
</articles>