

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<articles>
<article>
R o QIRA44ORflQS4o R 

>nerpages polyehronmfic effulgence that makes a rainbow look hke a lead pipe - 04mer ANINtomRandolphHearst 
HLIDHAMA EVERAV EE! spEciALDr)uaLcspsuc-_tde-Ttt.u.bty:c/tAvtrcs 
Thu 02 S41 :I Sat Ell Fri Is Apr 27 9pm llpm 11111111 10pm 2pm 10pm lupin 10pm Zell's (Live Tonight) 11011fiken NJ (201) 795-9606 Apr 2N Nazareth College Rothesta NY (716) 5146-2525 Apr 29 East L.A. s■ractist NY (315) 471-1148 Mk, The Cabaloosa New Falb NY (914) 255-3400 May 6 East Stroudsberg Univ Smma Awn,: PA (717) 424-3396 Ala, The Court Tavern New Brunswick NJ (904) 545-7265 May 12 The Globe Theater Norwalk (' 1 (203) 866-2999 Ma? 13 Nobody's Inn Mahwah NJ (291) 529-2357 
Mud cc-snail: DIN4e7cicartband.@aca-corrs. Want a copy of the Mud's CD? send $10 to MUD MERCH, 951 second Ave, 2nd Floor, NYC 10022. Make checks payable to Mark Czu). Want our free newsletter?: The PROCRASTINATOR Call the House oY Nina i{212) 7313-04S4 

951 2nd Ave., NYC-
10022 

rwallo \so> 
i SI 1 : cr SKI! N NJ 08558 
li°14110" 
r.q 
etet”s 
0.170A,r 
1106114Wildilish4WWW016410,1 
usiosmst 0 .3 Z z 
</article>
<article>
PROCRASTINATOR SINGLES GLIDE PARTS: The one-night relationship 
A Ludt of man 
ONE The Pal t (The Miners tea can make the effaces between ,• mine off IS a la Juan and thane off lie a Dean Mum I •Comb your Its • hide grooming ma. • tong an Asps colors and mast grease loci m your shirt. mien vote gut agouti to show Snag army as much as men lie hi Meats maws lie bag Stleaten The fan but Masa A dry • 4 is tab u MI•v•Isel as an hal, IA unrest 1.44iihs a. in^ ale OW ey 01-0 JIM ;Lana yobs cocky a orogen' loyal near et a gem a and, fee ample 
TUX. Ihe p the lobo.' int gala tan help tilt the o.1.M m your lava Inc rag Ss slate to not gang Mew at ill ■ •te eerie Inn t sawn ten much Suggest that since all the ben a tithed a the mph • all Yam why dint we Ins sin pack and go tack to an piece Turn to your tack and a has too had you can't cane nth us Leonard. since you ham to stork awns ' if Leonard tie 10 Tailed you tat be is sanployed. Lick hen hard sy the elan "Dent be Too hams Let spaustv be seas sae let Ow on won MS at you at east to only Ss on the comas %hat ha hand • MLA; 00 true knee as thr rambles on shout how she a Wit w soy with ha et ad lea sea thendstup Cs= VOW rasa what thew catershetm scab teeth meth tee in nig 'Mu at be at ratanth ram your tongue dawn my throat Take Your tam. dent thug Meat asst. rustilq off to vow thou lake vow tax that Mewl anxiously paha of to vow again m ti x,u sae hang some race • AS the you make a Ire half on hour or so and she says, •: tank I tout leave now. before I do senate. I regret ' Dam see 'Put busby" and get all thmerat and peat off Agree with ha pa vow nat and slimly yen sash I head to the doe, /I you be ha mate in the tight sn • sae cord will a be off nun 'Don't Be Too Mow • S.rnah. thou no too logy she with het away to tat amine a ha el Mu pons a scencelung ash the osit pas eu hi hen• 'you'd nu :made n, nisi hes will, the she as before Leave bar a mule now and take the rat of the ,u-park home a vote wrookla pale 
Thlta Set • The 141..wcni ups will help make scar Inylettattl ages • ding 10 itmanbC1 (Vet 11*-0, LAO n7-0 01 IL, •12a A Condom Hoar may elm Sas but you *said ea so ample :bough sou Moan% manarat ha Ice it be us art that the has probehly taken she TT hams beton V••• and thou she picked • winner tonight, her Jana in is everyonea :dandle As4 d she Sal am you is a sack s of lama not how had AM rudiment silly a It's up to you to ant y ourself !tote SThs et wane cluid-UMpar: afoot I lath an Oemismoblic sae a she bas one if panic and ten hr ready L se when the gets Iced a et we up 'En will oaks he and sae he rahn you an much different than the nelat who cared about noting but bang (Iwo an and salmi ac the fen subway back to Pr...then Of :am sou probehh will hese an orgasm anyway his 01 001 In. %Thal hat longer Plus flea hump se menses the .hared pregnat especially since as nml be sang a thinks men though I told YOU to rat baud •Don. he SAW to a sestiore Moo psis are dried to tell You when %utile doing somalung along they Jar pa *MU bah and slow Uwe ern take the 4, at the raw...lows Vann. We 'cobs do you MC or 'Dose that feel goner tow ha that sou ficubk and awned be auld be flamed and named Nanr• Dons he wad if what she want. seem a little nod there's no home to .hat you're capable of if you suspend vow moral saes taunt be • prude 
II You Edina these Rath indemes not ofth will Your asap reationship be rituumlh awaking. but you wall has. • I.4 teas saw dam the corning sem What Last' Maybe .Mai men take you to areskiat Lathe a. Iasi safe and etresthetw. 'ow, *ill came der Lt. Lisciot m • as of louse DeParas 
Pepe On 
IRO( RAS FINATOR 1010A-1, \ NI) LA III to iNs-ro),INCI Tivrry IN -11 II: IAIALANATIVII!_v CI I. V.' 'Nal) (Or I \11' 0 
Now None 4 thew asoduren *Iva be masted saOM,,A Napa trapsuson Iran other • a licensed pinu,,an M-mcked manta of the clays or c thorax 
I Mt I If they an they dun t know how to pat rented than tea had to ant n lundergance or the. gut no walk Rand than that printing has m ark ea flipping a falsMe cnntsol ,val. ass Rana tan out Sr walk of thee cell are Cnh passed Sine. as that the eons do mat Matt imeatinanthe-chalkrged pasts al be relined In have a fro else• solos sand home can cans the muse %IQ, ms cans-ea% Saha hod can inns the he area maw arousal a m an eases hymeneal blase Assad the ace of Nue act, can name a &Med • make hint a Pale • • peat nano, of a last of an seas man triads hold dear And if all Se fasla max ellow and blue thither and watch air eyes light up when they sat the inn s peen" they • II Net ad won tat II have a show dosnows and sena nom the ......Itsbis 1 i c 
hiSki UMW), AIL:. L.ce ur euacat el aeusaa• mums seeming came they a gale noes maga Ilaap Ty la swat neallag. bag sada cetthansher has in tbe dad d an MI cold cone 'see AAa the day dwell my Wow. ma Tm net n gems steer agair and Own II THANK YOI? 
f MtISIC Iry Mu lay to e dullard -Hey man vs W. Tan." 11e II tat • sleepy rut a0 a hand rola came and , 'Sher- Of earth tht:nts se ram web der euepaam of Led Lynda is crap ‘onettelees you goal u to gm& an bun the desire 10 b0:0•ne • MuMelall 10%-e hat Olt. %Mu and tell him to ben them down • in coma can Say An you follows% that Laud' Hoar that" Thai low ume Sun vote Sac dullaid -w have port • 001:11 IS be Mac today/ inso the bengig as You can a bask, acted a Ow bar and us to tinsel! 'Ma I tars a sands Sneed couldn't play one mare I should he the 'arras sew' 
• YHI/ 1.1IIST PLAY THE Eall/SIAL bade fa the 'Inlaid to nu pia into ha hauls& ethemated plzsgt you must ma yam in cabana the geutheen of sot. esyhmed coloring mlehl make •Pec7C01. 0...0' a Unitas/Leh tam mum you mum as up on tom anoutagh amebae foreign and arm ant an knowing me• Nou ins sod at the *dad mad sat know I aorta haws thotght of that bait. " ea he anuses w s phik•spto and vestal Meenasons As ha bag gas • ma he may aludAle •n• m10 44,11"17("0 came "117 walk a made pleasing and flat you Mal let hen hews he Suld wr tram a pro than loon/1h adopt the sine of say. an all-eaglet penal 
5 SEX Eats vets dullard Mews no much about thus topic a not enough. and we prefer he know not moth Sea a alas the meal penencla to the Ouse A ball Mob. ans. Damen the matt as of eta. easy hy en the sea-art el ma have thrown the bah and palate ands m tram tn a7 Owns-Km bawdy yon a &remota demise ash naked ask: Alta what. the "great" Sin seldom continues munterg 71•1•1•124 and to wane format and moss to St • oda lost cut than the tea. dials full of Sag and Ms Manhunt Hasa ways Meanwhile he dart sand the beauty end perfrata he CHI)": : have created upon the canna And slug of NI nail Nasal Maier As the french has "Tit es wawa acre She stares a at the ceiling and thinks onh of rthannyint ice ores 
e HORMONAL LMISALANCES Seldom a a tope as paste the been dealt with liall as awash awed  Me to Enfanurateh a act censor and • shun Mats an mate 4 all but unpusek lin war to draw the dulleal•da. gram it nald dos the -Xo7.one" which secretes satiate and dopaa and we vowels - Alas dear Leona s led fa-got to gne yin an X.Lone ' No X•Zone means no archaic ranteh cropping an your hilluemant no X-2 a mai to meal Altgangh mane dram the a at s a . in the shale o! the mast bathed in rht.a. nerves Siang :CC tr.: u.,, h. II,. r and 1..stlift.; qv •ug. .r :.. - . -01 i 9- • MSc n4. an- . - -I , J.- a -: re -- . sane' they 0 or r.. t. it Mt ad ye Pang a owl *MI a aleriounal to ethane nna gm lama, to • gam tem sea away. at. en Ides And no X./.as means to visualization of ea samigka between good And Md. beam bias animal smaita and the urge to tanend ethentude natal V. X•hwe aware no ability to a a sad lie "esclautle- even d you re pram rue You at know what at means 7 CREST PANS I ike all of a dullard. is seta fres cheat pains the resuk of a had Sea and pate Oath too much Sart ant Outland a hkeh to complain abort one of these awful temilants of Monteath& Isle and Sue their I) c,.......L1 be past ID deliVee • Zen style blow or are enightavnast "Iir, you ism ere to fa sue cat to! You*" You ark and then whack then math on the hack ben.- the thrulden If the Madam o silos on von you ea ate milt than can a state of higher C0111410‘00CIS DI vuu do not achieve this •arnittedh ad-to-man msuk math tour now notsthallard an of the mamas and hack to vas aputmad Thar nth dun candle and magic alai Sam swear to him the than ot the ha horses and of the retain A lea ate of the ea- tapas tracing earn Ms NA Ma an see, and of the macl that saw its .mw shadow and thoyght a au • groundhog The nib vat mat agerroinly with a strong la and beat hen us • cans • Elk:CAIION If nine of thee hand, can L at methods ale tamed sou • II. hut have to teen. yaw dullsd heck so IPA on aod pall out • new one Kaaba sec dullest do heats imatanng on thaw own so patips Las card or a Us it B I: mistit be paw the thing to asset NM wad pencil A vet het pact once awl, 'Put rooter a a ran a WI pares and • canvas. LI be Joan I tent the stretcher tame you set n back you II have • rat of an lag • Salad In a room with pants and a cats and 1 I be make a sock 01 Mt. Si be dent to hrea the stretcher of past event base he ma a back - Yaw he meant by a it saw nen to is des. Ms setaMrs frog the cruesuonablv tad 'School f a Ilw Merothcalh Enabled- have theorized and than bad the academia a mem men. plc upon than foe the tat The possehlai Sc an co erwhelang that the, Serf 04.• ••••• LIMAS haw mugs Jens The dullard son goad a look at all this athltesthated paraphemalu he could have ban mg to rule the scud could hne been kat_ • agenda at ken MI Om stuff centred in duet because he was 10 se he knew al: the rooms et hat hase pram to Mut the door ted go down and get a a 4414 lit in the se well-le Schen and at hirts•Cll into • etas llyn is hoe MA as you put yeas coal on sad Sad an nu the night be tun and keys • paenbanct an your any cat 'I Know arcane Net As Da; As Yoe Rally Are' In Ahe I- Piece a Kendra., • classical wan ',am Sc aght. Hz Soli A SW ' 
Promasnor. Aprl 1905 
he/ 
•`aerie‘ 
</article>
<article>
PROCRASTIMATOR HELPLIME: mime WITH MATURITY 
tannin. the aid of the b.:gaming ' Not if you do it nght Maturation can leave you like • fine wane. more potent and tasty as you age. or it Can leave YOU like an Wittig 'gritted bagel Many, hardened sad bland We at the PROCRASTINATOR have the PROCRASTINATOR as our means of avoiding the lanes law, but you. the tw env/something reads sliding ever and ever up the Loader to s nuclide alas, what do you have' Loath. you have us we're here to help you age in style to maim< by becoming less obnoxious. not less fin, to become more seffetell-dent. yet leas arrogant, to ea betta, and vet still feel sickly Here arc a few easy guts:clines 
Moke Murphy's Law Work for You' 
By now you Mow that ...erythema that the go marg. still Why not take advantages If you're at 2 rermarant and the waft= :1 lakmg caret. hebet op a streke and your food wig appeal instantly ir”tna: ,irtipily: and hyping for sunnt weather' Pack an urnric.14 Use it esUl. a will be ideal lor swimnung. provided you asn't pack a birthing suit If You want to wind up in bed with a stranger tonight make sure there are no condoms in vote wallet And what you're going out on the town. always plan for a duastmus time. You'll never he disappointed 
2 Pretend to, but really take nothing stmoush 
The Jokes on you if you take Yourself too sayousty Anyone with a high opinion of themselves is an open target for rdicule. if however. you're willing to ridicule yourself. you're • boring target Imagine how dull the Man Bros would find tormentmg Margaret Dumont if the knew how to laugh at ha own expense Life is past a bnef flash between lung stretches of death and sleep Why not tom the winning team and stay detached from the folly of the workaday world? 
3 Learn the an of Selective Incompetence and Surreptitious linIthability 
One uniquely American trait n the act of cost-effective work•shulung It is important to be rec-ognized for your abilities and vow industnous stamina However, this usually requires anon if some kind The key to camouflaging vow inertia is to delegate to tamable peons and to Yupatownplay the role of adorn m vow mt. requucitnaus If you convince superiors that a lob is !too menial, they will seek another. more anonymous employee 
MINT AID 111111.111 Felt €011/P11141Y, NECLICEllet AND tHONTSICHTONW 
by what was possibly the shortest literary coup in histon. Aunt Acid beloved and well respected columnist at the PROCRASTINATOR has been arraigned on charge' of %Timm loon', "ilhedeacy". "pow stenography" end "nueandszopy" 
Quotes one bloated Mexican official 'Er a citable> no dos &mega" which Aunt Acid herself might have been able to translate we she still at our offices Instead. nothing but her frail and hairless head could be teen ES the was shuffled through the usmcendental bucolic UM mess halls that constitute Ncetheastern penitentiary for Women where she is being held without bad and without official causes 
A brief search of her desk at our offices :mated possible shah and gave in a scoop only the PROCRASTINATOR could find -Ladies and Gentlemat" I said (me being there. as pan of the story this time and not Just a loafing reports on the Mama) 'Awn Acid is a man in de-pose No He Is Nor I was mailed by my own statement and sat down for • cigarette Cad thee know shout me' Was I a moonier. m disguise as a man or was ii the other around- 07 both" What had la Norton always told me during those bad years at the chruc' What did he say I was supposed to keep telling myself if I had another "their The faces of those wound me pew deformed and repugnant to my suddenly heightened senses (cont'd on page 1) 
NEW EVIdENCE REVEALS Mud MEMBERS LINkEd TO BIZARRE MICIGET SMUGGLING RING 
•, in I • el.:Joists home butibmari 4214 • 'bairn K °tuck brought forth evidence to support claims of the Mucus alleged complicity us the infamous 'Dwarfs on the Wharf' smug. sling rig prevalent on Manhattans bast Side docks of the late 1920s • I doubt its 011C Cal-titre's they were born m the lam swum' said an overmthustatic Mud spokesman Meplusto Dolores 'but all politica. is sacred so we gratuitously perpetuate any slanderous myths • 

Prograstnalor, Apnl. 1995 
AM I OUTOF TOUCH? 
If you h ye asked yourself this question incessandy (I know I have) and wonder whether your sat woe, pow-slacker chin? ideals and humor have become excessively self-absorbed. cc whether you arc out of touch with mainstream ideals of today's capricious poet-gunge 'Offspring' and 'Chem Lay' addled youtt you had belie' wake up and smell the lima or forget any marketing potential you may have The editoo of this publication were concerned with some residual benSitnIty left ova from their college experience. and they embarked upon a journey in quest of Complete Delet1M12114011 It n kind of like the backnabbing male-oriented retreats of the Reagan aa, but the opposite It as sponsored by Etna Dulwich, bastard oftspnra of the Speaker To apply send insane, letter merman due need of son spine and SA 95 to HRI.7 FORCE 13 East Canyon Drive Arlington. VA 38920 
Mae /—.d 


adlr  End, and Mas• Tough Enough? 

BEST GROCERY LISTS OF 1994 
1 From December 22nd Ginger Ale peanuts. salsa toile papa, beer. seltzer, potato chips 2 From March lit Teriyaki Sauce, string beans. cilantro, ohm oil chili powder 3 From August 3rd Frozen Spinach ill or packagek beer, pie crusts, ricotta chase. salsa. guacamole chips eggs. wash bags 
RINNTRS tis The Rita horn October were all especially well-cony nosed. but often omitted essentials that had to be picked up at a late hour, sometimes when dine was mere minutes rum the table Still, there was a verve and a flair to the braveness al "steak potatoes (reds camas, pinto beans. ketchup. asparagus" that defied normal linearity. 'hymned the typical banal references to mixers and beer and established a ace' of "nointamassamblage-oriche if oSeumre oeuvre" merecedentcd in the field of abstract grocery In waiting 
Pope Trois 
</article>
<article>
CLozz IF IQDec 
TIRED OF DIE SAME OLD EROTIC Ptak Chaser` Move fanned a you rAaratnalt 14.1104- asp earth oar new 1.900.%There.Werr-You' Phone Lam Get norm lee end talk for hoist to an onestnremeutoucally salmis love Mn 99 per Mina. call now because you've got • lot of calming to do. Do you knew boo hie * r7 When have you nor Ca rya sow ee aria speak le you AVM 1-900.Eitg-Trub 
ATTENTION SYRACUSE GRADU-ATES'. Did you attend Syracuse Universal and grakata tar gnaw Mk we would His to ny yea SWISS for yea diplomat Ras b dein, Hoe. her Can get the may, you eat of echo people's bathe Ram rut a SS S. Bachelor of Fine Ana. fed elan at 1200 for such rennet as -Doctorate a Median/ Folklore SSS eat if mann on • planet One day Sim only. brute sour diploma on Feb 31.1 to TAL Knierpryse Tempe/ SO Ea 225 St 
La I am wry I ate vow slug Ileac come home' • Lome 
Ill, Remember me' I wits the ma your friends all reared to AA -the Goa- when I crashed into your table at the dance Om ode boon Maga my Mena what I rcated throe moan hat that you woe the one 1 oat Mart me Pw) Pam", ad 
an me how to walk straight Sorry about yea dress Call Lion 3-D.09117 
WANTED Your money Please sad to boor Dumb bawds hos 23 Grate Sutra NYC 
HIPPY GIRLS TO WORK AT HOME OR OFFICE Many good.tneetrameed health yang women are rads to come et and straighten out Acta measeda lifer $: SO an bout you supply the wok. dark bee and couch-apace Y-16-0987 
SW) sating atuatay young 1.1, sr Is 63 who al asks my dna more the lake keg rename *Ma Wring on WY a' husband through tainted beneculart. and few thing Smokers o k Call 917-0989 wid at far The want lady waifs awn* sista nightbooth ' 
SW? Man Is rave than e ha pew Yee an a brave hale WICANA not afraid of my gnaw snore PhD * loos toe tee. it's mew s Wilsa No makers es cowards plower 67(766 
SWP wishes is fad ova-educated 3INIA who will yarrow Ulnae feadiesdy ha dull philosophy I need to bar what you dunk aka are love ad the laintrie shoat how nobody understands vent gams twouse so beyond than on and on into the rune tarot you pus in in the Hoot Lay hue 
tattoos, track marks. All these are Plan Ca Maga norm 
YoUNO PERSONS WANTED FOR TOP SALARY FUSITION1 THIS IS NOT YOU Case MOMS this ad gaily applies to more apettenced persons, Do you know how to operate as MASS 1116 twoduntor with • 14-he to 
drive and cad row SMOV You dot well. those dam don't even at See, we new ways of rant to the rah Now get MI of are and bask to McDonald,, you, you eon Pena 
ADULTS ONLY 
LIVE' NUDE' nIfOe See Live made female averts{ we is ad lea dance of hunger and desire Today u your local Zoo ICall 1-f00-who- DUO foe ash oe the soo name to you ) 
XXX XXX buobS )000LX.X.X Gas le tairray nosh's fen de fatal hi Sadie Amman Dona, 171 Vona PI NYC 
/CC( UNCENSORED SEX XXX Gad all ton; el uncensored az scenes in many classic romantic thriller. now all *Me at pose bad hairy Get in as the bot stuff. ad nose your rights as a tart. ' 
HOT GIRLS" (WARNING Hot gra should he cooled wit t ea • wattarandod solution. or • I ""01".11 pool. DO NOT USE SOL VENTS! If the bootees Mina MOAT gel In caramel clothing along with note of calawatton to Out.Macr woo. Haan Unnerve. 00000) 
LIVE NLI)Eoll -To lave is to he boat own" Nees life to marry' Not only does It aye on clothing apeftSCA, bat tea fun and tam-mina brecth' For a taloa* of shay mu aught moor call 1.179 0987 and ask foe He Who Peasant, lodgement on the Returnees to Monalgy 
VERY YOUNG GIRLS WANT YOU" Very ma trament young women we a-eig far you to help awn nuitoiehre Start oakum enough money now in that viol be able to and them to and bus them care wan • haw a hippy gal end lot some sun-these can y oar gboem all caskClean. mg 01 the palettesoul, read and wallet as all provided far you at no mu. charge These gob know awl tee need and it's not what you think you want Move me Call now, a/ you'll nova be disappointed 
BEST VAGUE REFERENCE OF 1994 w la Dort& of the Appalachian r. net this claw vague referee:e 'es and haemostat the Iota: /noun . when a Preelastuiwy recorta -ed to have • pen in hand sr esperello Jc ninnies" when oted from Swahili nietn, an , J this meddlesome foreigner - a deem:. to the Iwo that he husk t 'ade of ♦ bed in than three tat much doodad m thw Pthelone S Tubbs ol tut-) atslu was overhead to corrueen: re a an itch on the back of ma • ...eve in crawe et • lee,: )hn ink Leopold 
INVESTIGATORS SEIZE CONTROVERSIAL WILDLIFE FILM 
Say* OM AIMS Manta,' wus head A, cal won dm own toothe." 
Recently, a ante of previcsaly thought 'wilt sauna have now revealed that they arc quite antelhgent and base been rms.represatted through delibesately chanographed ....lente and ovenein enhanced fdrn somata in a h filmtrak. as as National Geographic and [hod At:abaci-an -They made an all fight thiamine • lot of money arras boo from has new ly paneled Rama borne He cordoned he nude ma t.4h).000 or ha slaying et: treall tams. • crazed dumpanthe, and ma ica.lusulted antelopes the Ion ea) the la-ad tar of an on sass Serenglieto entifirden oarsman Many caber Taws navy als• been rod oil. sonatas v• publich fornicate, enmetimes tiara each other mei mates. often with .ataatrophu auks in etualdt . •ccord:sag to spaces the wad anarna tend to live rain ety ea-ten.- etwen,et Moat ,,11 their ford is deli. ete4 from a local earring nnike ad the. mewl their Madam lone tone by the pool playing Tao and watching speong evmu the ma ga. he, mew about by wave of the ECC, who have reatheded to a newly retrial Loalition of herbivores Din coalition leonsating mainly of au.ons and vans plans herbivore) demands ea menthes be mope rat as Me forms of enough imitate that eating of than is &shoran and nolerabk Meths this efkrt on the., pert will ruse rarnpathy or merely het kten carenttr. Iola Appears. nt one can say When alai at a mem press cadatnce whirrs he was worried about hems called up on charges Ica ha masertnadervig. the alcremenuoned lion commented that be want worried. and gave a defiant thumblew Web-up 
Page Out, 
.4nd then the editor, bereft of ton:crud at .1 al vas it /gnu's/ by those he tore,' railed .,Mull, RNw foreal to !midis', the toetindeang dfivel of a chatterer!, roothaltzed mnispizatiott 
CALL1D AN IDIOT 
mood wages tee • sawn. et Mail come waded for you stone I was called an idiot ms me, • ben by any Mot wee • leftove slier s penappk pins 1, my gattnend what doe as end' 
:nth the many Amon can-epees ) ha of cold me IRKIdady the sap. ray many. apt was the toothpaste slips the sink and 1 mush rotary oe empty teeth 
kry anddla's bound far hyoid up tamp to clean it even se an white wet malehood m black molt Ma !real with en% cream man Iot'Sepad Pm& 
Called a Mot by myself, my biggest ann. hoping I fed ass mg tad. thy of treecken or Teeth women get tote the, lac • sate that doesn't week I repeat that line • thcaand ono. d cam t work 'get you at together.' doesn't work 
Mrn be I should go back to chat. 
Like an dice he liked you AM Earth. lime we went to akar tn circles trate Central Pat, the day a curd but stem outlet ord. my fees don't hat La an adiacould tame my man mind mob gay I could cave from late 
If I cold ay pa the tame. seed of pasta life away, I would be fate-'us not the cane I love • yd. 
I GIWIED FIISH 
Canrubal of mare I cansated with relish, gags that woe rN. c Igale4 meas. in Stays. banana sae releth fruY0011.31AC I Wed ?mayn't burger 
God hap me. Ion I Mt at all, fide fowl ad mound I dad not duattemea w aa dead ad his and pleat dawn 
I confess I as you foal I All the an the mane< into the Oath I cornrow I'd do A anal. Urp.1 to hve that's all I have God hdp me turn the ape aid I'm tasted 
Procntsbnmor. Apr{ 1905 
`owe% 
</article>
</articles>