<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<articles>
<article>
951 2nd Ave 2nd Floor. NYC 10022 I 
Procrastinator 

.N TI IIS EPOC14S 114WPABLgldgt../E• 
Navel lint skull caps: - Newest Fashion Frenzy? Mud Band to releas(? PosthUmous al! More excuses fcirdelayed cJict ribution! 
Procrastinator Disclaimer. Publisher is not liable for decrease in.quality of material and reserves the right to blame aforementioned decrease on Acts of God, action by any government or quasi-governmental entity, fire, flood, insurrection, riot, explosion, embargo, strikes-whether legal or illegal, labor or material shortage. transportation interruption of any kind, work slowdown, prolonged sobriety, lack of staff interest, fail-ure on part of readers to provide feedback, paranoia, unprovoked attack by Rodan, head lice, field mice and fried rice. Thank You 
Collectively jading minds from coast to coast (Hudson-East River) 
TNf itionyotwas 
HEADED YOUR :WAY/ JUVE Jary 
---------------------------------------------------------------------------
Beating a uead none wan a New vamp moat 
Bake the Cake, Shoot the Bitch: A Jungian Deconstruction of Lyric in Contemporary Musk An Award winning thesis by English B A honoree, Abe E. Piece 
Misogyny in lyrics is nothing new In the early somas, when Mick Jagger first sang about gelling girls under his thumb. or referred to them as stupid girls, bitches who mere mainly after his money and always ready to leave hie with a lethal dost here were few astanng young feminists who was really paying attention. obscured as the damning words were by Brian Jonend Mat and Mick's dreamy sawing. No such prettiness lends to obscure today's misogyny laden lyrics. however, especially abate the Mexican Mud Band is concerned, and the offense is let out with a con-temptible, hostility-evoking weer, the very purpose of which is often obscured 
Freud ono* mole that unscrupulous nurses often put children to sleep by 'massag-ing' their genitals in a circuit., methyl This really has nothing to do with this essay. but snit I interesting? And why did Freud mention this in his scandalous essay on the theory of infantile sexuality? Merely to prove his point, or to outrage and flale heftiest his stuffy Victorian audience? So then we ask . vary does the Mud? DI cam theologians and couch-femausts are stil puzzling over the infamous alter-ation ol the love Bet lyne from 1 should have shot the bitch on down' to 'I should have baked the cake for the girf (for further analysis and Dave's subsequent ratio-harshen, please refer to Procrastinator No. 32) In a strictly Jungian interpretation, be cake represents the womb, uncooked, unbaked Infertile, unleavened. The male 
promos me near coma, causes me case 11.1 eye, manure me cases emu a pony los. In which case it would be the oven is the womb. Nov wail. No, the oven is the womb and the ;Jensen cake is the phallus. Now I got C. What about the frosting? As the French say. 'The frosting we save for last' And what Old of cake. I think the woman in question would prefer any flavor (aside from coconut) to being 'shot down' by the big phallus symbol gun. Note the down. which is opposite of up. hence the degradation of women The seed that the Mud is planting in the *bitch' is the bullet, seed of death and dis-like This is the only way to get the woman 'down Perhaps down off the couch, on her pedestal, even down from her precarious perch on a rock in Central park. which has left the agoraphobic Scott stranded below, very nervous. 
By moving the symbolism to the kitchen, the Mud prove they have the courage most males lack. They leave their power sphere of male dominated world and enter the kitchen, the lensik, side, and the nucleus, the hot tie tub of that kitchen, the oven, the womb, which is where they lay their cake. The cake is a positive metaphor. the laying' of the cake in the oven denotes a future wherein the cake will be presum-ably eaten. unless perhaps Mark made it and forgot to add the eggs. Alas, the question is moot. because the Mud didn't bake the cake at all! They lament that they should have. similar to their lament That they didn't shoot the 'bitch' They are all frozen. like Narcissus in the pond. like Sleeping Beauty, they ate cursed. enchanted, lacking the decisive capabilities necessary to do something Aiming at the gas party empty handed, they mill around i the back. nervous. hoping someone will offer them a beer, -We should've baked a cake-. Scott whispers to Dave. Now they wil not be asked to join in the fun or "Pin The Tail on the Donkey'. Alas. d they had just entered the party with their guns ablaze. they'd have all the prizes 
(Note. Abe E Piece's essay continues id well over two hundred pages, but soon after this passage begins to wander off on unrelated tangents. including an overlong discussion of the Freudian significance behind apple per a la mode Untortunaleh, he never annoys back at his anginal thesis. So for the sake of brevity. we end the discussion here.) 
A message to aspiring young filmmakers: 
Hackneyed Plotlines and Pseudo-Poignancy Can Work for You! 
by Bruce Fatly, the Suburban Cynic 
In today's cinema and network sitcom/sitdram scripts, certain elements which appear to the reviewers as refreshing/original/universally appealing arc actually as old as Aeschylus' Tcvas. If you are embarking on a film project and you are are stuck in preproduction with an unresolved plotline, or are finding that rewrites are destroying the integrity of the characters, use these historically proven sub-plots, twists and motivation changes to flesh out your storyline. Under careful observation the scripts of Frivolous Romantic Comedies. Hospital Tearjerkers and Crime Nailtuters have only aged in terms of technological usage of props and social trends. By following some of these hints and guidelines, you too can lure the artisti-cally blind public to your wallet. This month: Hospital Drama 
Key Characters:  Young Workaholic Doctor of unspecified race/gender, grinding his/her way into an Epstein-Barr related premature grave 
Middle aged, baking, slightly overweight, fishlipped male (or female) patient wrestling with fate (divorce, estranged family, cancer, career, etc.) 
Pretty Boy unshaven twentysomething intern whose drinking/womanizing alien-ates parents, staff, even the patient/ nurse who has a crush on him. 
Pseudo-Poignant Revelation Unrealistic, Ratings-Oriented Catharsis 
"I grew up in a filthy ghetto/trailer/barrio fending for myself. I watched my broth-er/sisterlfather/mother deteriorate from AIDS/heroin/alcohol. That's what I'm run-ning from, Dr. Kershaw " 
"An EKG can't fix a broken heart, doctor." 
"Yeah, I know. I'm an alcoholic. A loser. I'll probably never finish med school. But I am the best damn osteopath this hospital has ever seen " 
Falls m love with passive liberal and transfers stress from job to home. This pattern oscillates to keep character inter-esting, until actor decides to leave for movies, then Epstein Barr sets in and character dies. 
In last scene, patient is visited by spouse/ daughter/employer/doctor and notifies patent of sudden change of heart/remis-sion. 
He gets the girl(duh) 
Some Other Key Elements: Frenetic camera jerking during emergency surgery, older, calmer General Surgeon who acts as rudder throughout plot, smattering of medical babble and hyphenations, tight, glistening cntrail shots to confuse viewer's empathy with nausea, hypochondriacs, homeless people, AIDS, roof jumper, psycho with gun takes doctor hostage. Always remember 1. Doctor-Ego Problem and Nurse-Dead or Dysfunctional Family 2. Everyone sweats in the operating room 
Page 2 
Procrastrater. June. 1995 
---------------------------------------------------------------------------
U 
PROCPASTNATOP'S GUDE TO DECONSTRUCTIVE VIEWNG OF MTV AS A COUCH-QUARTERBACK'S MUSIC NDUSTIZY, POST-WORK PIPE-DREAM... 
Are you watching MT/the right way? You should watch rl as a seller. not a consumer Understand the realty behind I, the fad that they are selling music and bubble gum to YOU. Question to yourself how edsctive each sales pitch is, what makes you want to buy a certain brand of perfume. or • CD? How can you learn to sell to yourself? Why glue twenty dollars to Tower Records Not to own vocals? How can you gel other people to spend money to get your voice on record? I decided to research these interesting questions by spending a few hundred hours with Mud vocalist/Queerest Dave Parsons in front of the television watching MTV Alter pang down and forgetting some of his more vague comments. I have compiled this handy checklist. which may prove as indispensable for MTV watching as televised sports is for former athletes Here are some handy pointers 
KNOW THE ACHILLES HEEL OF YOUR GENERATION. 
AGE GROUP ATTRACTING IMAGE EMOTIONAL SELLING POINT FREUDIAN SYMBOL 14-16 gins eras winsome sexual insecurity Potty14* 14-16 boys Cindy Crawford surging hormones Motorcycle 17.19 girls Cindy Crawford Narcissistic Euphoria Hone 17-19 boys Ugly while boys w/s.ki caps Sexual Insecurity Gun 20-22 girls Eddie Vedder Maternal Instinct Pine Tree 20-22 boys Rid Gels Sexual Starvation Nose Ring 23-24 girls Backwoods Lesbians Sell-righteousness None 23-24 boys Ugly black ion waski caps Misogyny Pot-Leaf 25• women Hoops & The Blowfish Love Sunset 25.. boys Sheryl Crow Melancholia Beer bottle 
You must bear in mind that what you buy on CD directly affects Mist you see So beware, you might love Hole for example, but if you buy their CD then in approximately six months the MTV airVfaVOS will be flooded with woozy. obnoxious blondes. Just look at Madonna! 
DEAD 011 ALIVE? 
Recently, Southern patriarch and honey threaded tingle deeper Burt Ives passed on The editors were surprised in finding out Ural ho hadn't died long ago. As a result other names came up. Perhaps you could help us decide who is dead and who is alive. 
Example- A. Lee Remick B. James Coco C. Zero Mostel D. Ephram Zlmbalist Jr. E Jack Webb F. Lee J. Cobb G Debbie Reynolds H Jordan Catalano I Alec Guiness J Dave Kendall K Bernie Koppel L Spin Doctors 
Dead Alive M. Melanie X N. Phyllis Diller 0. Chuck Barris P. Chuck Berry 0. Abe Vigoda R. Twila Tharp S. Joyce Carol Oates T. Don Ellis U. Miss Piggy V. Frank Oz W Shelly Winters X. Charles Nelson Riley Y. Dean Marlin Z Charles Groble 
Dead Alive 
1,7101VECO TO liTC1111 5ITT COWNITIVIT101 TO% T101IT 71071115T 51C0TD 117111:1 51101CT 
*The key is for smokers to never exhale" says the dizzy pundit A few patrons of the T.F.B. (Trust Fund Baby) Pub in Resin Gulch. Colorado emitted a practically audible cheer as self-appointed local eclebot John Lagreco announced his candidacy for Surgeon General. !Agree°, who last year announced his candidacy for the Colorado gubernatorial race in a moment of desperation. expects "a lot of sedatives" as a result of his inauguration. The confused and attention hungry ex-snowboard legend limped up to the by with hopes of free whiskey, a cane blanche gratuity provided to visiting VIP's in the small ski town. The bartender grabbed Lagreco by the collar and delivered an expletive-laden diatribe. reminding him that the dishes in back were most assuredly not going to clean them-selves. The disinterested crowd declined to comment as the broken leader shuffled back into the kitchen. 
Procrastinator, June. 1995 
Page 
---------------------------------------------------------------------------

mad 
4R1 CHOICES IN TOE C4 CE h 
no cabbage head. Art clicked The basest crumb of beat had stuck in ass thrnal. and it gasped! It tom the leafed ventricle walls, and grasped, as if drowning, straws. It broke, the frail art, from that one my seed, that II lodged lie. that single beat, and the cabbage heart just pumped relentlessly on. past teeing, past dreaming, past extinction 
Why did the Alt have to de in this way, a pumped apart leaflet. len-ven-Ificle lay in shards at its feet, in pan and par-lay. the relentless and ancient awe from the day. Moving in the sought after, the high after, the Earning lavers in their Sudan evening clothes, the fashion experts as left thee own designs. the plentiful ancient beforehand millions of fathering, nathenngs, so wise and behead the susceptible to treason who gone fleeing to bed, and raised all sorts of hopscotch in the (rat tree heads, with millions of fortyish pigs in their low. and zircons of Iambsbread and basted to know if the subject was wiling or bound in the night. it the peon was bran-washed on Saturday night or just left in the locker until there was light. with rhubarb he waked with rhuli-gel he faded. he itched his own scratch and thus doom was pealed he felt the wind lash and the blade was serrated if tore in he back and from backwards he sailed, swimming through cow pastures without a sail, just Skins of fishes all bed to one tree, and millions of birdies all hed to one bee, and sang about horseradish and shredded salines, and balloon-shaped star-chil-dren and horsefly moonbeams and all the rased lepers who in trances appeared, saying they did dream and al through the sewers that filed up with steam they saw shadows of loved ones who'd graveside went gong, so many years ago, and then N was snowing and in the height of the SOFT whet clouds did they say, they saw U1110 and Thuma and Hoist on 1V. But Horst vas • puppet, and that they didnl know much, they ddlnl pew Bo. But Bo had contracted with Nice and Sears. and Bo had more money than 28 years. and collage cheese reindeeis sad over the was, and everyone hero is missing thee balls. they should run out the from door and see what they can, they should run out for cover, and over the Lind to buy butter and bread for thew boys overseas. and ram mar-malade for the rich folks in the streets. and in sound of a chimney pipe they shore can't run 
In shores where no waves come, there's nothing gets done. 
PSEUDO-EUROPEANS ARE SEDUCING YOUR EXI (or "Turtlenecks In June") by Ivana Tenjitt Metro Angst Correspondent 
nary huddle around SoHo grottos will names the Amid Mks and Mezzo Glom°, mulling plumes of bluish smoke while shrugging and Mapping thee rigid hair our of their bronze faces They are usually from Pennsylvania or Connecticut and led shekered high school Met They 'lopped college. moved to New York, became biller that they had sud-denly become small fish in a big pond, and in enema (or social rein-lorcemenl and approval, they adapted European postures. accents. diets musical taste and aggressive smugness. Now they are clerks, hostesses, floor runners and office gophees, who barely eke out a city hying Their diet consists of slivers of smoked gouda, assorted fruit wedges and iced white wine. meticulously nibbled and sipped at gallery hponimp. They furtively study Kwasawa. Foil*, and Tinuffault films every Sunday at obscure, claustrophobic Win forums. Thee indifferent upper-middle-class parents boost their income when needed. (Like, If they want a culinary gadget from Sharper Image.) Their apartments are sparsely decorated with low leather and glass furniture and two-color paintings. They abhor answering marines. Wile all of these louts are innocuous, their sex life is ravenous and unscrupulous. They change lavers (and persuasions) nightly and should tar kept at arms length, for birth control is a bete not among this Misled Little cult Condoms are detested almost as much as circumcisions. Should you come across one of these chameleons in a tavern or book bar, simply say "Non, pieta' and head for the nearest pained Here are some of the telltale markings of these thinly veiled demons' 
MALE FEMALE 
Black turtleneck black tailored jeans large cranky black boots 25-pack skinny cigarettes closely shaved sideburns crisp halls* perennial Ian 
Putty white stisrnbraiess) sunglasses(dangling burn cola° peg leg Caen pants open toed platforms dark lipstick poodle perennial tan 
Page 4 
RI-35K? 
ARTISTS DIARY Take Two: This is the recently found diary of the noted artist and fraud, Erich Von Krappe. Erich, known as 'Enrico to his one fan, claims to have been born in 1904 in either Spain, France or Bulgaria dependng upon his state of intoxication when he is asked by one of his many frustrated biographers. His He has been one of general upper middle class luck co-winging with a definite inspiration derived from delusions of grandeur, and a whole persona that seems possessed by another lime. Unfortunately his own laziness and general lack of latent has ensured that few if any of his few . d any, paintings are over seen in today's art world. Nonetheless this diary, recently discovered dropped into the Sotheby's mailbox anonymously, is of Interest to art historians as well as just the curious and horrified. because for al his shortcom-ings in latent, tie himself. was truly a piece of work, whether he was a work of ad is sorneffing for YOU to decide We open these journals in late 1994. whore Krappe (pronounced 'Cho:raper, or some other outlandish way every different time he colds someone for pronouncing a wrong, except when the cheer of his loyal student following. "Knipp° s Air is involved) is still laboring at the creating of 'Acrylic on canvasses' a chore he will soon We up in favor of rampant egotism, loutishness and tiresome self-promotion. 
3/10/95 I was tremendously inspired by the view from my window the morning. I currently overlook a rather dank alley and the lack of sunshine made mo so uneasy and apprehensive that suddenly it seemed necessary to do something besides sit in front of the TV, I paced around like a caged panther. fighting on the oncoming shortness of breath, cold sweat, and claustrophobic honor I thew so well. I tried doing the dishes. but the soap dries my hands so' Then I remembered that I was an artist. no a great arta* who had been languishing away. It was the ailed within that I had been stifling who was signaling this panic attack! Lo. he had woken up within it by the depress-ing sight of the dingy alley! I lunged for ray box of brushes and tubes of paint. I filed a cup full of water and looked for a fight but to see by. I cleaned off a plate to use as a palette and then cut up the box my paints were in and gessoed it for a canvas. I was anxious. trembling with anticipa-tion all this while. wondering what beautiful mad vision my panic attack would aeate. As I waled for the gesso to dry I looked over the aim, for i was the cause, it was the very inspiration of my Muse After 10 hours. the gesso was dry and I began to select the pants I would use The fast one I selected, yellow ochre, for as purity and sexiness. wouktn1 open. neither would the second! Soon I was trying to open even the unsexiest of all pnts: Bumf Linter. Even this would not open for Enna,' They were at glued shut! I tried and I tried I held them in a tub of hot water 1 pleaded with them. I danced for them I played the drums for them. but they were glued shut I honk this is seine sort of lesson. Eventually I put them all in a bag and threw them In the East Wier. Tomorrow I am going to a pant store 
3(21/33 They had a sale on blue paint today, alas, that Picasso gets up eerier than I do. and by the lime i got In the store. he had made ell with the lot! At least I managed to talk that dim-willed shop. keeper down on Burnt Umber' I know I said it s unsexy, but what do I care about sexy any more? I can make anything sexy just focusing my perspective' I lee it because it is good shot color; it e my fife. Perhaps the school-children were right to call me trap- instead of thre-ppojli. For it pleases me to smear burnt umber on the pretty virgin white canvasses. I revel the fact that I am a filthy creature. the shame is synergized into power' (In these next few entries, it is believed Krappo was drunk and hallucinating on whiskey, absinthe, or any number of other hallucinogens whose wens predate our current pharmacology 
4/12/33 My ignorant critics go to great effort to tell me how unpleasant my burnt umber phase is lo them The fools know nothing of value. That paint was only $2.95 a tube' I still have several hundred WSW 10 go. This is no phase by any means. This is a mood' 
5122./76 Somebody said it best, 'Every empty canvas is a masterpiece • MI I managed to do with my tat• ent and filthy Marshes is to sully the nice what, world. Let them that demand my 'mornings. them Mal pay high prices, lel them cal me -maestro' a Mingo, in of color to the emptiness, a giver ot form. yeah Thera leachem But I know. and you dear diary know, that the void is the only form, the MAO IS often the only color and often is often enough and then we're really oiled., all is while. I'll sleep a while canvas. mid the tined forest. But by dawn it had sprouted greens 3 There is no form for Enrico There is only shape and a sketchy idea of twinging anatomical form to vend that guides my work But the form is always lost in the wind. That *why my donee-tors say my work has no meaning, why I need to lake an meting comae at the craft colege. They accuse me of developing my paintings poorly 1-lah! I tell them. Nuts to You' Not one of my paintings has ever been developed at all' What I have done to the poor white canvas is simulta-neously give and lake away arty chance at being something. One brush stroke later a master-piece is arevocably ruined, on brush Woke earlier, A is still unfinished. Outing the moment between, the phone rings. II is the grocer. 14e wants money."You're money is lost now, you idtol • I lel the men, 1 should charge you for the canvas you just wined By the end of my humorous telephone harangue he is so amused he brings me up a gallon of wine and some bread. Soon he is trying to steal my wife. I whisper to her in the hall 'As long as he promises a discount on but-ter And sneak up to the loll to wreck yet another *natant piece of canvas Oh why don't the canvas makers just see what I am dong and stop? Why do they continue making if necessary for me to devastate the face of the ad world in so blaggardly a fashion, 
3/2/67 I am besieged by meats even in the loft. A spider watches my work coldly from the corner and when I beg him for commentary he says nothing, merely scribbles notes in his little journal Publish what you will you contemptible misinformed journale! Perhaps he is just waiting for the inspiration to build his web. If he starts to spin a web I am bound to feel artistically intimidated. and I will have to crush him! Oh how I hate a love hate it love it hatove it all! 
Procrastinator, June 1995 
