

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<articles>
<article>
July, 1994 Free of charge_ Special Windbag Issue 

/9.94 PROORASTAVATOR AWARDS 
The END or giwerme000? 
INNER CH/l0 4,61/S1 
COP/AV wow MEC/OCR/TY 
Dec Schwves House of OSSCURE REFERENCES 
Men THE 11/4/9101/7S. FROM EAST ORANCE 
fx-moveneo OR Ouroneo? You 01C/01: r/FOYE MAMA di AlVOA! twierli MOREL 
MEXICAN MOO MO 
THU AUG 4 9pm Desmond's New York NY (212) 685-0901 SAT AUG 6 10pri. Nobody's Inn Mahwah NJ (201) 529-2357 THU ACC; II 9pm Desmond's New York NY (212) 685.0901 FRI AUG 12 10pm Starr Cantina Rhinebeck NY (914) 876-6816 MON AUG 15 IOpm Nightingales New York NY (212) 473-9398 THU AUG 1)( 9pm Desmond's New York NY (212)685.0901 FRI AUG 19 Ilpm Ludlow St.Cafe New York NY (212)353.0536 SAT AUG 20 lOpm Nobody's Inn Mahwah NJ (201) 529-2357 FRI AUG 26 11pm 7 Willow Street Poncho:stet NY (914) 939-1474 FRI SEP 2 8pm Lemoyne College Syracuse NY (315) 445-4526 SAT SEP 3 lOpm East L.A. Syracuse NY (315) 471-1148 FRI SEP 9 11pm New Music Cafe New York NY (212) 941-1008 FRI SEP 16 10pm Old City Hall Oswego NY (315) 343-9453 SAT SEP 17 8pm SUNY Oswego Oswego NY (315) 342-3389 
t Lehr. vocalist/percussionist for NYC's Mud Band, is currently living in Zaire with a tribe of Elvis worshipping pygmies to prepare for his solo album. Want a copy of the Mud's new CD? send $12 to MORE SALT, 951 2nd Ave, 2nd Floor, NYC 10022 Make checks payable to Mark Czuj. Want our newaletta?: The PROCRASTINATOR CALL wont) TI4V110l/St OF MUD a (21 2) 7 5 9-04 5 4 

951 2nd avenue - 2nd 11r. flew Volk, DV 10022 
David Maxwell 222 E 17th St.#2F New York.NY,10003 
"Alnohrtely the most frod pica of tripe on the market • •Rupert Murdoch 

2 
</article>
<article>
THE 1994 ANNUAL MOCPASTIMTOP AWARDS! Yrs, it'. IL flaw of year .Min slackers esercrwhera shed their scup and 
Jon hnedos Wen Iwodtnq off to Jersey and the gala 2411. annual PROCRASTINATOR AWARDS This geor's line-up of dim elan and Las-been-Lefore-they-inns include flo Marlin, Scott Lehr and John "I forgot mg tuxedo, mon " LoGreco. W.II olio suck fetching starlets as the notorious Tracy Mossy, Ilse demure Dotty Heady oral the sullen Ho Vennyhoddy. The big press is of course, Doctor Twilight's scandal-ridden Lowing-out of acting as host for this iron ceremony, clue to an unfoeturote case of insufficient °Loki-poisoning. In his piste, Ike unrelenting Drocroslinator ocoderny warchal high and low, and then just whom., was closest to them on the couch (in onile lo gel rid of them and molt, more room), that hapless announcer for this soon C011fr FTIORICS willbe o bag of (Stew-doodles! AWARD FOR MOST PITIFUL ATTEMPT AT SOUNDING BLACK Ti. Inks. Dow POM0415. of the Melliten Mud Bowl &a Lehr, 01 the Mein.. Mod Bond 
AWARD FOR MOST PITIFUL ATTEMPT AT BEING WHITE Don Marlin, of the Moak.. KA Bond 
AWARD FOR MOST MINA. ATTEMPT AT SOUNDING BRITISH DOPPIM Bona fir Ins mien imitation of thew Iwo girls he awl of o Lan It makes Icanu knows sound IL Pniwed Button. AWARD FOR LOUDEST SONG NEVER USED IN A FILM "Beall*" 64 the Mak.. Mod Bond AWARD FOR MOST UNINTELLIGIBLE MUD RAP Dow Pones "Chodamily" Roo MOST OFFENSIVE SMELLING MUD MEMBER Joa ladling, Mon BEST MUD SONG EVER - "Procrastination"' WORST MUD HANGOVER-Wed. a 'incised nitro hospital drops 

WORST MILO PAPRESSION Yes, go. End. MOST OFFENSIVE COLOGNE - Canoe MOST IRONIC DEMAND-Ea wallow welt Le "Stoptl Reielt" 

BEST ATTEMPT AT SOUNDING SINCERE - Any ol 1%...n topratlan ottabirponnong awed& ~Sion 
BEST PROCRASTINATOR CLASSIFIED - Grp.* meinaanne to Lin a Own. 1993) 
FUNNIEST ARTICLE (scary Era) 50 AI Cs* Nen -SoaN lAw (Aigp.1.1993) BEST PROCRASTINATOR ILLUSTRATION M0140 Kahn. Coe, CALLeolion lesur 
WORST EXCUSE MADE BV ERICH FOR NOT PRACTICING BASS "Disc &le My Stn.w." 
BEST EXCUSE MADE BY ERICH FOR NOT PRACTICING BASS NI ialtraawford sink." BEST SONG BY VAULM EFFORT - D...64.1" BEST MUD CCNGA SOLO No DUMBEST EXPRESSION (psailsq Jain ma You diode) MOST OBJECTIVE, UNUUDGMENTAL PROCRASTINATOR ARTICLE - No minewes 
BEST PROCRASTINATOR CARTOON - End al die New Mimic MOST UNDERRATED NYC DELL Con.1 23.1.15d, MOST ANNOYING AFTER-MUDSHOW HOMELESS PERSON - I wit ennewLee ken nowt, lot 144 Dew poi L. on 16 wit Id WORST WURST IN WORCESTER- Pat's P.4 Paco en Par, Gin 
Th Thud reopen atal wane a &actin Jaaloado al eceviori Npa. mad Int jawnoi Si Oa Sac rm In Corxnzoon. a ALUM 4 WA, Tao and /awn Maw Sabszaan or Ant. Oiliat. Wan Inensata. snonne4 tancansa uaJd Cann C4/03 Oa acun, wumbunasfr ad ad IRA wafts! yob taw One w sar.lien.fivin 
Page 2 
tow imem rani limalaml sena la imemal 'psi mem I. i. way 
i'rnuastutator. July 1994 
</article>
<article>
51f4L,Epooto. ?ART TWO HU Eft) OF 31,14kEtIOOD 
• • 
insny a our readers rave angled from our past sane advice ec Much Mal they we now no longer Inge llIrvie we aU congratulate those lorturate. sexually salatial 'galas we can aireay her glom Wining 10 us tot advice. Now can t make 4 air ter 'Mu 4001 ■ wart It 102' Well W• 901yOu on lrvil aril, we 5 cot you al In argon u....- to showing you Int NIA/ ant to leave your aver well show you one or two ways how not to Well show yOu how to thee trio upper hand. and std end up gaga Or 4Chy 1.biSilff °WO,: As IM nets of new love Sege. One panne In romance tome lo less sin . ewe candy and ga.ga then Ins other It as than common for Ns other Penne110 in 10 SUrOCate them back alto their former Vale Generally. the been advice when tong SurOCaled a to not trash wound. as the weeny deepen your banners dean. to "rot let you go' Spay piny dead until your partner goes 10 the ballroom. then rangy gel bean and run on to pin Me Peso. Corm II you ha yourself In la annotation or being the surfocator, fenwrne to apply prewar at the Vara% Ow yarned:a spot Si be tome of Its nog between the ogarbone• 2. JEALOUSY: .. 040w to ran It ark for your if you gel mere attention room the Opperle sex your rennet oars flaunt this in there face at every conceivable OppOnunly tin will keep the Nano& or power taped in your lava II yes partner gels in e) Attention try to overcompenne yalh heavy angry and serpay Whine sorry IMMO your breath stare moodily no your Onnk rata Cr bag %Cabill. a Ns mutt party you go 10 a that (Mend gel tarn to pay you more Senn, 90 Deck to slip one Suffeewilon 3. D 145 ins": 'Absence rakes the newt Now Wren' as Noy say Most Ma ins plat I no+ los to be Want, as tat allows 'or an actual personsSty to be reemerged no something more Carat* will the enuiths day-100ay tarafiergua exeMenCe For sore. a nary rangy ci a face and a renallsclina 01 a fun nary • preamble 13 actually bong with a real Pena For NIP skickler bras* trough to in and stay in a nationally. %lianas,' becomes necessary thganarg. as caned in the Sacker Dictionary. a the an of rennin; ale 5 rumba old Wanton from the ogled ol WO 5 anon-bon II should be eirsbyed whenever yin pan begins to act 'Mature and Marts Waring you 10 CO tne game AS lha il bound to haiblin. I 16 •YpOrtant Ile aura* 10 Doan datangrg almost as Goon as then now reialiOnehip togs Some tips When you and your net mate are being tamale PI your mnd warier cal. Ott about al the gar Nance you could be Ong will youf time Respond to every fluallOn with "tan!' every answer wan 'Go?" end every declaration DI love with 'whalever " if you mum say 1 love yr:N.100*D* are 10 ea an "I guns' to la end When vOure Se Ira lace Dela your gar, your rag racing Riles away and they make a 100m anemia to "midge the gap by along you win you re thinking oi. maybe even oaring you a bribe of a penny ante 55$ and say 'oh nothing' if they newel In trying to roan their Or Caere/a Dreten0 Yours asleep it mat Cana ark. pretend yarn 1 dean t' we 00.0n1 wOre., all young!! .or Mee 4. pfikErts: Wang parents is • no-win canton. The ricer they we to you. la 
4e:S.,1/4:KNA) 
Who mould rave trough that in lea a per an could be so completely mama gad Dy • Kean that Wall only margrUgy reoular in the lane TM Ni at rte-parvo has existed lot oath years and rag coon a nag 01 Malan and carve cuter elMUes for the past tray or so years. But for Ian that have mastered the an has shorty become the perfea Icol 10 SeDi ankle the Coned masses in Nppydom from Ma hardly earned monies As an undercoyet member Or this trauctulent mass I lo,Unaal a ValuaND Wan or two AG I transferred from one word to the nerd. I Ina to peer agar ht bMAN ply' cadelc colors to earn the reel don draped behind a riga wall 01 Una love and sappiness I was pupated lOr my gurney Deans* in hand, and reedy 10 taco tie furies neat 012E-DYE FEVER 
Tha au vrve Coiled and we wore ready to I OW The rag was made up of a plethora of latent !hat Intruded Lis Bergman: a Comedic Jewish mother *Basin in earth of fame, fun, and • husband MN a knack rot spending Don Martin: a lag time nethe "armor. funny man, and as we later learned, purveyor of a host el Curran loth emanations Beth Katz. a power WNW and pager rot the Dacia/9 augh track lot our journey And Me JONI Split?: undercover journalist 10f the Pre:Manna 
The brat thing we needed to Co was armalkele 1110 the gaga liOpydem' 
frtkrannotar. tidy 1904 
Our pan was simple dthe as night. don) Saar tank developinga unique &tenth, and devour a case of beef before 10am the next marring The Wale0Y worded to perleCtrin With the help of Coe powerful sun. a lose from the peace Pew and the plenary mentioned ennanCeMentS, Dy noon I was as land and Burnt as IM 'eel or the DopUlabon It was now Ong HO the games to Cann 
With Someone elee • trusty dog at my side. Don thanag our horns ban and the ors sawing the alconel la the days Conikumption I set out to explore the treacherous surroundings There were ventral everywhere Some were Yang liegyee. $01110 veggie ilaulthathee, are were hippy beads, anything you coal 00•••:th want and most thugs you dot needy ad not want Each vendor wad and errata Ike something damn Lag n New Yon City 11 e hard to imagine buying load from a that an Man some or the roach tilled tine dining establishments around here Places where the roaches an eo bog as to snatch Wool right out 01 you ?MAPS. *al II In ant ol you. take Our your wallet and leave an enornowe tip But In rvIOPYclOM• you Can Ind and buy loud grated out 01 the harder Of *Omani who haat showered on years? The greet thing a that they don) try to hide I In fad. they Saver gee I. in one gingen lag shop they were ailing the Deadhead lavahe known llepalaS flitiOneunced neh-Parl. TEE.loser wtuch corral of 25% vegeta-ne. 25% dog. 25% dna* talaillal and 25% descloue Tali 100% VOW and of carte al of Mee establishments paned all Nana FDA regutabOn• 
One and that 1 noticed was that everyor was very !rangy and gullible. Mad Don and I boa song used oars 10 ait same 
lees they realty ate you Sonesereate tot the by moon° your int iracr-sac - a nombie one Lauri and weal 00 Clothes. Duna a 10t and nuke test CoMMSNA Ito Thee expectations we be vastly kneeled From then on the Waller atonal decency sail be a oaten Surpriseas opposed 10 al expected norm 5. 6111U}I-(OFTROL: In addition to security and bye and all lhal. Thal, any riasballb Wary mean& a sex yahou condoms The brii hoes on the pril the boy ghee Ns PAN Condoms away to NO sit hands, naming them ate. unit)! gored Nee But I ha comes Ns eventual pSyCnOtiC inertias that are bound 10 D01.01 the owl due to lagaerm prubraceulool mapulabon Of not length hormones 1* thicket mare Can recta to nor mean hystena by either /al airy symp,ppori, convirting net aria • cortriolory Mane The One MI bag rim Moat to t.c Deng iirenitalve but that can reed to trouble, es in berg expected from then a, thervorm lot endless hours every lune ear laic aria Mere at MO PreeraetnatC4 Sagest you try plan le) Moon val enable you 10 gel away ran irrational Demonoto Denavor. The orb no drawing a Mal I she may believes you, she 11 use it ari, pent. cation for eventual multalbn Or your Omega fILI4IFD-corisok; loolalionshns we a boat struggle arc the flret 5 points Iona are I hew to was n None 01 them however. cone close in imam lance to mind control In a prolonged Male ol Intimacy wan someone Many 'canner are *pence between psychos resoling In illind.nmocInCr You find yearn.. .gray natant uttennd No MM. Sages, undenianding ears Others raved:rat Carnunra Uon, and. al a nay krenng natinctrvely ea in the crowded room has slept MN crack other. When the sort d reiPpon la in pace the ad lurrolair barns Your east Del to gad your own nand erg ad Contrary to sour restrol*. and Swan 00 at wag thhge INS Way you wit ban be daghtfully 'unbreakable' and your companion sy be slagging lo brand guns and dominate you Once the occurs en. Ilia 10 sae WM UM your Myer' is at Ina most Secure and addled and then IoM rem in • war ma.. canal rranclone 'when are you wag to rears you cal chyle or 'Why dor you rust anal Val. aka from me. you nave no tar YOu then reggae them that yc.. wont leave, a! Wag not 41 la next In fan HS ION as they gal their 'ea' feather and buy you an ealellatIVe dinner They all be nand they cant aye without you and you all be in the luxunOuS ratan of darling whether or riot they Swan cOlf(1.11$10if: Do these taCtice seem is bge hush? Baby you've got a lot to Lee the Man Map al's tar ln POW and W.V. Sea and vIdena. ViodUCtive aware and aid Wins P. two and two together and you got lour. and at en? A iol of leatetand tang a Innion anon al natl. a We snot of vankey cared On the night table You got .1 age blood, a few laughs and a Mang Vila Cal But NEWS Ile as they Say. Lase agne and awn for love I you were and !pull save money But a you want to pray the puny be prepared to net Lose Cash mane but an the sex yew whatever your sea Both Wee win! Lon and war are tne same Love the wawa you play NM your aye, one Its natural to leer a 101/0 roetay *lag well the anon rkrt7 Remember lo play for though, lug use the Me LIDS you leaned here only When you feel the barn 04 powers sipping 10 your ODCOrsentartnall Side TheyII be and abed too. because no One lien 10 have I he upper hand WO long (1.1to everything. II gels boring/ Remember too that as long as you both keep your thane open to the lore you snare, a fa Mara and pray falling will pose DO neat 10 your ntitalOterlp, but will rarer provIO• all NYIU•Ing Way to parmi the time between your Maus, Iniedudoe Peace' 
group ri • agar higher tax bracket there avid have been • huge number 01 pa-pal gang non in brand row coypu-der c *MOM .01 nINICI IOW !YUGO ActiMlit the ClWilltY 01 our Neelfell were guile mon :7,01'01010 any !ma 01 bullshe was oath [Paved In fact a neabOring dogs urns was MISIPI dliglte00 as recentlY goad Deer and the clamp Teal* WC knit as Ng a the dry one* A* the gay poised on the sun the alcohol had reduced us to MOOling idiots. what made Dueness even better Both girls took the opponunly to pass on as Don and I COntnued 10 pugs Out "Magi Mar' OWL It was Closing in On Show time and we needed to gel • prime Ocean Mona' was on ow mra It was in this new Oa-Hon where we encountered the grilled cheese Nail This woman had all the Can and lax ol a NYC tan *Over. and that Was by far her mat charming charac-tons& She was bating out command to the Mena hungry Magee like an impa• Ufa brownie choreographer 'Step in line, people We are Beat let's get a together ' She was Penally wearing the pares in net group We knew as because all the mete were *easing shale Don finally told her to shut up and war wee athaned. OW that IS a story for another tin. Now we were In place and the W10* had begun 11 is this quiet time. when you have the Nance to collect Mal you Can see wan • pay song on in these places Snap the smell. the drug*. and No stupally. nap is an unartyla thaw The theme is prog The harverlie win eel angroods They'll Wean to you about love and brollwated age they make • ?5% prowl on pc or, onsaapecting morons I knew a had to be ecieleang bean the must. It was IMO 910riou• discovery and my 
0000MM:1 One with My inirrOUndmett that Prenatal me to pas Out for 20 naafi making up with si severe hargOver Don dualy ISO me OBS and the show began. I was a new man and had one thing in mind See Sal! Sea' 
There was on bodus horn the snow nm Oblate aboncra the ranee Ranted about Ou 11110 set up 1 had evervallna in coral and the drooling Itches wero ng out Of the Dane cr my Nina. Sate were thing out of there eke • 50% oft sale in the Paramus mall I was dancing OW commands "510 teat* baby. Chou It out, check 1 our lay, you gig on s. you DOWN it!' Don lollogng my lead Said nothing and continued to supply the Men • was a ntair SuCCeS• Even tie grilled Cane Nan was OVOCAT*117.0d with py As the Crowd born to anise we al relaxed. drank and Sake of the good old Jaye wren we IMP *apt. Yes II was all DOCOMIN) Clearer, I had Caught tie-dye over and n fell pretty 9000. When we made 11 back to the Cal. Our faces sole 110,11 constani laughlea we thew we weal not soon forger the won, dorlui trip The wag in the Car would Me-ant us from that We managed to nags the parking 101 unscathed and needed naps* back to the city The night ahead would brIng us sleep ahhh true bliss' Even locand the keys in the at could not put • frown on our ening faces It was thanfiran' In all Is gory that was On out muds If wee bright summer fun. the &nee Or teal floating ever so 1$ty In the air 11 was psycnegniC tan. the naafi fa in Our &Wean &Id IM money In out bookers It wail soothing warmth of me-SpOrstatalty. n was an Inepletoelbry, ykibly COMINIINg NO It sits tie. the fever and I was spreading 
Page 51 
</article>
<article>
REVEREND JIM JONES, AEROBICS INSTRUCTOR 
Hello. You may not mown/ me, but in 1978 my son Jimmy poisoned 304 innocent people in South America 
Lass week I got a letter from him. He is now an aerobics instructor in Emetic. 

ooKroft T%VILITC COUNSELS TOE LOVELORN 
Twate is a Mensal practeotwr of Haziness and Ineptitude and teaches saninan all over the country without ever leaving the side of his TV. Occasionally he provides desperate tenets with a clue to thew uwn belligerence, he does this with moments of pristine clarity and absolute disregard Dot coherence. 
watoeseo 6Y 'O0 vast 
Deer Dilute, Stupidly, I graduated college M only 4 years. With so much party-ing left undone. I avoided area-choices and escaped to Seattle to became • gunge rocker. Well. I managed to meet one, and he man-aged to steal my girlfriend. In despair. I eagerly boomeranged tack home to New Jersey where I will live, with my folks. My younger brother. all moved out and got girlfriends. money and cod apartments. I work pan time as • temp fun [cal pharmaceutical corporation, cleaning out the animal cages. disposing of the coign Needless to saw the smell of death is on me and the women know to keep away. Dow an I cape to New York, get a cool apartment and a patient girlfriend. one with bad judgment and • financially secure future. - Guilty of Encesa 
(Insider the fillies of the field They mil not, and neither an they mowed Nothing compels you in walk, and km walk Ibt, knowing mu ate on the path to success. Stop. Rest. Your CUITCIN path is bat Eat at MOM Chores- Restaurants Consider the flesh mu conoone. the mgr.. it his slept in, the lonely nights as wept in. The misery char Wm demur an be redeemed to transcending love! Free the bents from out their ages and smuggle them to certsin freedom. Free the pip! The pigs an sword Freedom rings! The Pigs an win! The Pere-Pig sows) lie tiny ss he drinks the blond of decent fanning men. He drinks with kne and than the way we never could drink him. Think about it 
DM NNW LOOMS 
Dear Delta. Why is IN there all the attractive single men in New York dont want a girlfriend? Are they so suffused with their on sense of self worth that they no longer require • woman! awe they become, in wane perverse way, their own rumen Urn talking about hetaosexuahl? If so, why? And what can be done about it? 
- Curiously tinder No Therapy 
Find a man who an only he attractive when het ovumd ova and hell be yours forever. Aaractive mar ger enough frwrabk mention from ALI. the women they meet that they door need say one. Ugly men gee NO tameable summon from women, and need • girlfriend so des-perately, they become uglier. Find • man whoa in between and reach him decent grooming habits Shine him up. and reach him to unclench his Jew. Over rime the ravelling will die down and he mat be too bad Fa your effort. mull have • dement boyfriend whoi scared hell be ugly without mu. 
Classifieds 
The Procrastinator pompously reserves the right to refuse any material that makes us look bad. 
PERSONALS 
SWIA, very. very young and impression-able seam enemata WF to nourish are clothe me. eventuagy to send me to C06101 WI men with occasions Mess and candy. 
SWF. bond with dalim went sena other Wfli to join Ins h etetninIng Ism dating sew singe Me urge they isen so behave Ins humans Inatead of teeth some boons Fmough of se Mop, Virg mica too Cal Mamba at 506-9095 Ire MI me Mem you wool be lin Seat*. 
LOST Erich's personalty Last son November. 1993 Call Winona 460-8437 
Faze 4 
PERSONALS 
AreSEyed vIdeonale U seeks labels+ MO bowl or popcorn. preferably with Sags soda and gorgeous ea cubes. No more let. warm ones please! Also. someone to get up Ind SIM the Into, Ing CM Nebdsh Naive M 987.0645 
Carr ONCE? You amt need rhythm or lam to nee E CM Canes Law Ai klot Swim at 487-2947. Aak lot Ent 
PART-TIME BRAIN SURGEON. No espwisnas. Wel Wan. Stasi Innwat► y. Cal Joan 1 (I®) FAT-IIRAIN WANTED: Bo* guile let Don Moan to My all there away. 24 hourron cal Cell8coM676311112 

_FL 
MEXICAN MUD T-SIORTS NOW ONLY TEN BUCKSI heck owe** Wert nee inkrblact shin. cleat 111/4/1•41 shirt custom order• available (212)759-0454 MEXICAN MUD CD 'NOW WITH MORE SALT' ONLY TWELVE BUCKS! Hoar Warr. Daughter. 'Shad Pride% 'Fee and SloOPY. WM. a has wlual as your Mid tavorlosr MEXICAN MUD TAPES 'NOW WITH MORE SALT- ONLY EIGHT BUCKSI For you 1,61.30110 and oar Illenth9 Aloes re. der eon:meal purchase sambas so, wading eery. 
STICKERS ARE PRELIM MEXICAN MERCHANDISE 951 2nd Avenue New Yon. New York 10022 (212, 759-0454 
I‘TCWOLUYIi 4. July 1,94 
</article>
</articles>