
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<articles>
<article>
FREE! 
JUNE, 1994 
New York City: The Pit ofl. 
Modern American Culture 
JUNE, 1994 
FREE! 
ROC MI AM  
MEXICAN MUD DATES: JUNE AND JULY, 1994 JULY 
JUNE 
Dates listed in attached flyer 
</article>
<article>
WELCOME, OVERLORDS OF UNDEREXERTION This month we hope to inform as well as entertain fellow Procrastinators with some facts about the Mud's homebase. the thriving metropolis of Manhattan. I have squeezed my obeekthargie staff for superficial research, tepid critiques. unrelated digressions and unin-spired philosophies on city culture. As the editor of the Procrastinator. I accept nothing but mediocrity for my catatonic audience. I thank you. -Max 
GOD FOUND DEAD 
BABY AT SCENE APPEARS CONFUSED 
Isink to cod my sun-scarred face. 1 tank below the place I know. I hide behind the yellow. I hide past blue Into dark gray shadow and wish that Lcould stay that way but no I'm bound to float back up. annoyed at my hammy. screaming lungs. I dream that I could needn't breathe to sleep so still beneath their feet, these bathers standing next to me, shrilly shrieking pool• side sonnets, hopping heachtralls, splashing, thrashing toodden sharks deeding (tinny. limbless never-lend is nor robe, this carnivore who swims an me is locked in glass and cant swim free past humanness to lash as it would like, to unite. 
To snap the Fun m two halves and laugh at the ensuing darkness. Ha. 

God. as trwttpirod In a ream moot 
THE MANHATTAN MUD BAND The Rants Ot A Stoned Accountant 
long ago in a pious not so far away, the Mud was spawned in die veins of the Stones, Allmons. and Chicago coven. Ahh the humble beginnings. Hector was everywhere. There was scarcely a surface to which Hector dcks't affix himself. (He did have olittle help from the faithful servants of Mud pro. pogondal Whore is Hector Agave now? Exiled to on occasional appear-anal in this here tribute to the docker? Oy Vey, The influence of Cis Utopia, this docker's paradise has been good to he Mud. It no longer resembles he slow mud of soon to he adobe huts, but more stinks the funk of Manhattan grime; mud laid to rest on this city's sweets by a JerseyJeep with oversized ants (or was it a beat up Dodge named Becollaht).This mud takes comfort in the trenches of degradation itlias corns so know as horn.. The Lando of the visage on a worm spring night fosters the frenzy for butt shaking. Cheers! I've been accustomed to being the danc-ing fool Fronk song of floss of course the spoon for my nose) Why not? 'Don't hold bock' wasn't coined for nought. How the woodier wean of the surface To haws the fair city _ behind once this eyes have feasted upon lifel Yeah, when apricots bloom The breeze. hooey with the summer's sweet smell of unne, carries the rhythms of distant and not so distant cultures. Resurgence of a mindset almost lost long ogo is taking place on the very streets when the mud rest omongst two hundred dollar shoes and dirty syringes. A resurgence of o time when music was a soul's facial expression presenting intik Nice mugs, boys. Tikes! The groove is strong and getting stronger every day. There are some good bonds out there, kick Enjoy itl (lkomrter the eighties? It could be that bad again some day.) So gel out there alt you slackers Shake your potaso'in' Tory Boy asses and support the Mud and all the other greet acts this city's streets have to offer Exposure to elements is good Don't overexert your. self, of course. The slack must be cherished like a fine bourbon 
Page 2 
NEW YORK: A Slacker's Heaven or Hell? 
TO the unfamiliar. New York City aoesn'Tyem to be sort of 0 place where 0 slacker can really ',MAO'S*. smog and traffic. The *lost•pac•d• I doesn't seem compatible with the slates Meth.° it. then, that New YOrk City is Slacker heaven?  , IM most slack round in telluride. courstacto. rar Well. John. there might be mare trees out th•r•, but r - less putty women. You and your ski•burn•cl cronies around In front of the TV oil day; tn• 'mountain' le Close and there ain't o woman In miles. In New York. there II t much to do that even sitting on your COuCh feels dance Out than skung..in New York. nothing is banal, so eve' banality beelem•s something to be treasured. When •ri Can you a drunken tight. SIX gorgeous models, three homeless junkies and foul mutionair rging on street COrn•r Oil In one minute. and sill fee red. feel proud 10 be bored by the biggest, loudest in e world? 

lake a tyolcol Friday night for the ProCrostinator s Inc Mud. one out Mena, Soy the Mud has tne n grit o and we're organ; to see IMIWTot the new Monte Core First, we meet of Max's-tot some snots at whiskey. Suddenly, It Is very tale Milo doesn't even go on until One. Ond It's already 12 5911 It's for too late to go owl That's what I soy. I'm airady too wasted to wont to go out. They drag me there anyway. I'm birching and moon• ing but then %filo comes on and I'm Suddenly a dancing fool. Now il s 4 am and were standing Out on tie street. drinking beers from one all across the street Now I'm wide awake. It's 2 nours past closing for any other bar in the world and we end up In Some uttro-trenay bohemian type piece. t gist home around 6 am 

Do you think yOu could stay Out Oil night without really wonting to anywhere else but New yolk? No. In tact lust to go out at all anywhere else you need more energy than a New York stacker vou know how weak the sane will be. You'll stand around. waiting for a 3 chord wonder bond to come on. you'll steno forlornly at one pretty gut bitterly at her five boyfriends. anxiously at the bah game On the big TV serail. and then wonder home. deeply depressed. hoping you make It hams in time tar the late news. or the tail ono at Letterman. aw Yolk is also perfect for me SICICk•r because II puts everything of your fingertips. Literally. because although everything ISO bleak (twee. YOU den t even have to leave your apartment to get It. In Other towns you Can get a Para delivered here you can get your laundry, whiskey. malt. groceries. OOP*. Yride010001. and more whiskey detiveuitdo And picked upi You never have to leave your Couch •tcept maybe to go to the both•oom New York it's loud and it's not always nice. but that lust gives the slacker more of On excuse to stay In his room and read comic books mon. when he's finally brave enough to venture out: right around the time any Other town would be closing down, aw York is kicking in, with gat. 
MAX FACTS 
A recent est for English and New York Ciry geography was given to New York City Cab Drivers. 30% of the present Cab Driven in the city failed the test 90TO of the people arming for jots as Cab Drivetskiled 
•inator • June. 1994 
</article>
<article>
Non. This fit miry seem sew arw you probably that other manes. Me "Where re Day Tees new 'Four Freda' Or 'Semi By Mo' should ourry, and yet yeallodscaon Is so mIlthil•f-
MAXIS TOP 10 PUKE SCENES IN MOVIES 
h could lee aided somihrtg, nreggge MIC-necks w inlet lona In Aura Now sorry Ito Ito ray Morse do low -ow which chard with a mirention voratust Nee ovty .1 vodtdinar party favor. but dso the Wok ewe pow hid body Function pot warble on maimentan screen Id lot) Puke scenes usually noir dan people ore dry& haw. wen smelled a dead body, or. possessed. hove don loo frock or ore 'argon ally cliswooght The ore some rho... telt, think you rh enjoy. I &qua-hod oil thorax who mode S so a x-et. That's eheceing Yoe one, even wish to watch Ilese colas and foie your favorite stars os twy pore. on tomato Simply non drinking whiskey funnels on hour before the more starts, averaging one every ten or rtes. lt works for at 
The noting snows isot follow VCSUME- The physkol roof inn haLotaingq the acre's nod. COVEPAGE The rodwn Bonus ••s for his REALISM Don re parson kat al trough? Convulsive/ FACIAL DISTORTION: Are the midis slockt &mind? VISCOSITY' Does thy month word stringy de Or lOpocoe =iflitiZS Very nix's-ION Must be nerd I. Tarry Jones from Monty Python's The Meaning a Life. A motwpierecinformorce ha' changed my Funk I used when I first sow this wane VOL COY 
2 Veronica Cortrigho from The Wades a lasswich. the movies plot careens wet from romance to horror to bloc comedy, Cortrights vomit is phenomenal h is ddhcolt to teaks a power boot tooltsbc hose a &ontol comer° angle, bet this one curs the monad. with cherries on bp. VOL ' 
FEi 
SFX:• 
3 Linda glair in The  (so • . The frandmosew of oil puke scenes. Probably the best projectile sewn, • spawned estop:Widen to Spit ►io VOA *"• 
COV 
Sfi:•••• • C Thomas Nora tor The Hitcher. I first watched rho ewes wick Syracuse Whiskey Gm Jason rosesketi. old we lowed the scene in which C. Theses finds the slaughtered komay on he slake wagon so we cuireang Wet cram:wad rends fere: fued"134 hour. The nokswe produced is Wet, as is dr covesuge. 6• C. Taos'low is hysterical. Carn REAL ID  
S loom Derr in Wad At Nat Dens doe a double purge when she gets on abortion in one KOMI. Olen Me' n Ih• next. LAS s•* 
FD lakhougts Own's face is manly &fetid.) 
SEX " 
6 Glenn Close in hotel Attnsefion. This is one of those emotional weds when Glenn sees Michael Douglas playing with his daughter. wife and dowirborsiew 
REAL FD  
SFX 
7 Anna Paquin in The Mew° much calesion was mew on 4.41 tender wail's other golden moments in di. onatyricent Fin Phoweror. I will always norm-ber hr pAing eggs ono booth. 
REM 
VISC 
B. Saiplinn Font from An of House 'fore it Flounder, you irked on Dew Weenie • VOL N/A COV  
VISC N/A 
9 Tommy Chong en Up In Smoke. He says his nom* is Itemacrocipk, man.' VOLN/A COV N/A 
VISC-N/A SIX. 
10 Spolcfrg Caddysherk Spalding donis clubmansbers' Wire &inks, Men pules Mao Lino mired •NvI4 said VOL (impled/ COV N/A 
MSC N/A 
Procestanator • June. 1994 
AkISCENE 
bylaw/yes KmerrArdwerre Arena. met die espeeth hp scones Maid • had; Mutt the especially may saws. AR renen we subject to re.werpreuner 
DOWNTOWN: If you walk just a hale ways past the quaint new ow...numanisitha (33 W. Hooded with its tunny exhibit of PtyPost-Pre-Pws-postmodernism works of Jacques !ammo you'll find. right on the corner of Howson and West Broadway. a most interesting ethnic The exhibit Is, apparently. the leftover cast offs of a recent wort. by ConiEdbon. The scene is of a broken barricade. a small oil slid/. two discarded pizza boxes, • smashed pylon and SOCK warning flags lying in • rain puddle. The obvious intent of this small mas-terpiece of found object eon is to pose the question of negatsvapost-positive viewpoint. Is the passerby a sKUm or a victimizer of this scene? II calls into question the concept of electricity. The viewer is made cognizant of his/her own powerlessness over power. or whether one's on power isn't out at home. What do they mean, then thrown away relics of the courageous blue-collar men who give us .sorcilt While most pedestrians pay scarcely a second glance to the forgotten, yet conspicuous lad inconveniently located site. true art fans are floored by the seemingly effortless array of garbage and forgotten pub le utility equipment. Most of all, there is the tragedy of its temporality. You feel in these fallen beams and snippets of wire the very frailty of electric power. It reminds us all that we we just conduits of Wine massive force. that God is • Con-Edison worker who has left us behind, like a discarded chunk of cable. and moved on to service other trouble spots (Front of Eric's Putt 335 West Broadway. exhibit will be shown until the cleaning crew arnses - •••1 
EAST VILLAGE: In a small head-shop on eighth street. there is a very interesting selection of teenage rock and roll wants. cleverly amused, ander ■ long glass display case that is worth the trip for any art fan too tired to swim up past 50th. Next to Dead•unignined butane lighters are a colorful selection of bandannas and hash 
popes. The juxtaposition is obviously a taunt-ing reminder of the hazy neo-higgy cubssm• cum-pharmacy deliria of the late. great Howdy Dew D'e. The very transitory nature of the roc►w-roll supply world nags out. as it did so well in Dew Iris famous sculpture.) Gut ligloss A Cherry Pit  The exhibit is in the heart of Jersey high school punk stoner flambe hell.. It reminds the Manhattan an-head of the lower mares need for heroes The newly legendary Kurt Cobain now joins the ranks of rock's grew drug users, his race on bandannas and biker patches new next to Led Zeppelin. Elvis and lean, and as and on, until you get to the water pipes...(Mottammed•s Novelties. 334 8th Street - "•) 
POST-NO BILLS WOODEN BARRICADE, 2nd Avenue and 50th. In a row of plastered-on new Kate Mau Cabin Klein ads. which reseal behind her creamy Goddemetos figure a crew of scruffy looking bald rappers named Onyx. The juxtaposition of pristine. impossi-bk thin white girl palection and angry Mack youths photographed in grainy. gaudy color is as powerful a piece of street noise as (ibis An Baroque ever dreamed of beck in his day as graffiti-terrorist street guru of the Back to Back and Back Again movement that flour-ished briefly during a hot evening in 1992. Are the black rappers in Onyx angry because white Kate has covered them? Or are they angry because part of her has been ripped away, maybe their (avoid pan? Maybe they were happy under Kate. protected from the elements and soot of New York and all of its grime and pestilence. Certainly all but the most weight and race conscious are happier drooling over Kate's soothing eyes and supple limbs than looking at yet another gang of butt. ugly black brawlers. What makes this dam-aged poster layer-cake into an LS Loosing that behind Kate's bikini lurks a bade of angry black fists. You can almost imagine their anger giving her strength. their upraised anns carrying her slim white innocence aloft. Venus walking over the Black Sea_ See It now before they plaster over something else, like Ke•ny C with his anemic grin or wone...(vacant lot, West Side of 2nd Avenue between 53rd and 54th Streets. - """') 
r s 
• IMMO • • • • • • • ANGRY MUD SCORNS -I PROCRASTINATOR FOR • IGNORING THEM 1 The Mexican Mud ONION &tor reers4Iter INS 4 thoo•h you probaoty coup, nag hum the or, twat have made veer] threats to the PROCRASTINATOR staff that r may don't start &no more • adds dawn so the band as opposed lo WOK about the meson& Wee of lnll PROCRAST1NA- • ITOR slate. they we *Vara* sponectald We hare   al   fin PROCRASTINATOR   here   bid   our tol but can fen wiry Sc. of wenn to wed about the Mud man. Shedd we attend ma lan-club* style enders -my Dream Date Was Don• or tie Was Dave Parsons'? Let me tee you girls. Meese • Dew Parsons awn as glamorous as you may task Or 'What Are Soon's Farms Pangs To Do • IWen   Ha made' Do Yid may want   as   knows As   Madera   of   the PROCRASTINATOR.   you   hewl haw bra us when YOU wart to know about the Mud because WE already iona• them. and WE w outs razor *Ws about word° On so •I LSend all correspondence to: SELF-APPOINTED GODHEAD KUERSTEN • Im■ 951 2nd Avenue, New York, NY 10022 • • se •  • a • • . • . ,./ 
</article>
<article>
ASK IDA 
with Ida Vennyvt,:i 
Ce Dew 10o. I - bre is MAI °OM. I me Morn everywniris may pay I Mat Dens Mangoes*. Out I'M vornee a I stars w Done pens we I get Pregnorat owoully. Annie Tudors Worronohbl 
A: Dew Arnie. fm grad you 0100 Mal Quedlon. tars Aid SOY I know how YOU Ms/ Dann *tiny. I (nun remind you Mot your hormones ITICN nom o tendency 00 get out of *nook Though you colY gre1 Vero* by mare Ce 0 Penh. you could di be On Wm Wry 10 at 1AM educe a Wren you see Donl run to to rem ono Ormond Vol he ploy sorneekrg by the Pommies. if he e de Cato 01 you. tat Nm Mot you Mok Seth Okayed mot beast and woe Wet to boot, MM. Ms. you want ever get precool/ MOT Scott a 0 retard story • and en WM* Nporof0 entry. 0: DM W. Con you clear won agtnsl rm novng wm my seer, I soy snot Dove from MMe are sane guy who played tey000,01 tor GWAR. My ester 10v7 he W010 Ou0ert horn trel10500Se Cain yOu pews oleo MaluPT Conased. A: Dew RM. Wee. fm wry, bu you're both wrong Dave horn the Madoon Mud pad was seen regJony on rho noon Byre show 'Bo'g You Box' docing 10 Pt Oval Moron of Love iscregover by Dana Doss Soon Lehr woe 0 mars ol GWAR and pored ATM" on Few TVs Dress s Oms You can now wee them both at Demotes Tavern on Thiunclay nights 
titsbeuRA pbtt 
MEXICAN MUD T-SHIRTS NOW ONLY TEN BUCKS! (Deck inverses shut white inlubledt shirt. Neck Ink/red min I custom orders avallieble (212) 750045e MEXICAN MUD CD 'NOW WITH MORE SALT' ONLY TWELVE BUCKS! Hear 'MayoN Daughter. 'Stupid Pros', 'Free and Sloppy Why. a has vir-tually all you. MW layettes! MEXICAN MUD 'NOW WITH MORE SALT' ONLY EIGHT BUCKS! For your walunen and cw imering peas re, ths ecornoal Pus-chase salads, wet cracking clam I STICKERS ARE FREE!!!! MEXICAN MERCHANDISE 951 2nd Avenue New York New York 10022 

• 
SOBESKY OR DOPESKY? 
Sanity Mos been an important part el the WM Of WWWWMO Wwww popular Si the after sch00/ SNOW 111141011 But this phenomenal becomes much more t Win It Ms date to tone. and affects One 01 the pratInent party Iowan todonlew The irreverent Roane J. Kalman. So I believe the sum be enact Sawed (slang word for • sober person) or demob (slang wo 10r WI Idiot)? Meehan Itellmen, otherwise known as Sew Bro. the Brannen a Reverend Bra of CNC al Lem. has, as he cab 11. gone Sonata After graduating here cot-tage and Indulging in the many plenum el tee west coat Itemised. he woe a Job et • private school n the c.net Nes of seem MaiMeChalielk The Dusso aloof. letwer tor tat err:Month dtsturtild. e5 Msg, end mrlatby smart . OMNI body. is the place he now calls home llitillayew pea alit MI dM MS Mega* brought on by the cceetent irowmprehawitle el hit lenglIme en* end braimal COn10111001. Jan Lep= (cMataied hits cheat Mort Wee c• the PROCRASTINATOR). 1 iNnts he moped he pee bulk' mid tauten° • he w•erre Wee at the ellewous Chards of Love - 'but he Would fit del In.' TIM sere to be the consensus ol twee nitro tam hen ea woe se the Met circle or the Mud Coney. "Ire Me a cue Si about One swath away horn a pie; sentlatt Pedate, long tebesandSsiter. yes, ho 'ref bawl the edge. end Wends and Illare concerned. Koala has taken many steps to nd hernial of he recent kepis* at deetru• lore "the demon weed' and Me *oh-so-polenlekewatsr. n tect he is on the twelve Sep program and racoons weekly peschieldc *valuations The dadacau Mends are Seldng is why? *Drugs are the lewd of ha problems.' sal ese meet talbent Omen Barren. 'actuary I flays thought they heaped? YMW panpM mull understand Is trial this is a job and It m m no we an easy job to do, awed* for am Bit  Si merely trying to Mall Inner moral values in the Wee Cl 000lueed yOuths Thera a crock.' says Dave Parsons, can player and Ve100 enthuliest. 'he's just Wog to score wen the young gases' Yes, a is hand to be and even hotter to understand. Steve Rro may be confusing the schools begets wets he own. and Nee very snails to what happens m a cult 

can scums once 'soy era od the %,..0 mtroung wee 

Redman has been seen at venous Mud showS Preaching and discussing his new land Ones on a frank end beans dot now because the whore S imiebrat-Ing Day.] Itereth thrall? he was recently msouoted MCI showing the bard a 'kw, pence he was mealy called Guns. Power, God and aloe People had smart roe and was away, NA that Is no different horn he college days 'Why would any-ale want to be sober,' aid Dr. Twat" sow peering over he half empty flask of bourbon 'woad any chaser to Veer Indeed, that tS Ire chteshon we 'ace Where is chaser are wtal happened to Steve Rio? We believe that he will be fro ad phase we pass with mine-el Carnage dont Ile w e gen a lot ot expenence from hi lob, and be dunk and slued in no Ow et at. But as an weekend camel lo • cams and he drives sows/ beck to erestem Massachusetts. the Man age angers Solmsb or Dopeska 
Classifieds 
Publisher's Note: Max reserves the right to refuse any ads that fail to reflect the twisted and confused morals that the Procrastinator supports. 
PERSONALS  Lonely skull moth seeks well endowed condie for twisted sere-nade. Box 364, Procrastinoax. 
SVIM seeks dream girl in the ;Corm ai anorexic pole blonde with inlet-tactual and psychotic tendencies. Must not get too close or 100 For away. Don't call me, I'll call you when I wont to she you. lust you flooding this makes me Feel trapped I want out of this relationship, later 
Pao- 4 
SEEDY 900 NUMBERS  XXX SAFE SEX PHONEUNE /004 Did I.90 -HOT-HATS $3.00 per minute to talk to sexy young women who Ilk* it rough AND safe. Once you're all hot and ready, we tronsler you to a loll free 1-800 number for information on proper condom use. When you're ready to play it soh, we bring you back into the steamy, but row safe action!! Gel our and educated at the some time, and learn to love it steamy. and whit (You must be over 18 and non-Cothorec to corn 
SEEDY 900 NUMBERS  
Tired of weok mixed drinks= Hate liqueurs* Call Sassy to get your rocks oft your drink 1.900-DRINKME 
QUALIFIED PSYCHIC will predict your fufulre! I'm a well-led guru and palmist who knows all about YOU! I know bow you cried when they took 'The Son Pedro Beach Bums' off the air all those years ago. I know the exact dote that it will be on in syndication Sworn' sez -- I.900'389-0948 
RANDOM 
LOST! SWF desperately seeking lost breast implants! Lost seen in my breasts but now believed working at the Boltimore aquarium. If Found speak to them very firmly anti remind Poo that goy cannot swim. Call Mary at 334-8967 to collect substantial, ritectikroonod reword.  APARTMENT AVAILABLE! Downtown location_ Easy access to narcotic traffic and subway. Fully equipped with walking water and sleeping doormon. Only $980 o `ewe month I (+fee) colt Lyle Peoltors/ 675-9087. 
PrOCiaStellator •Julle. 1994 
</article>
</articles>