<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<articles>
<article>
Procrastinator 
July. 1995 
"A festering hodgepodge of stimuli for the uprooted, post-modernist, existential-ist, alienated masses." -R. Crumb 
SPECIAL "ZERO INTEREST EVEL" ISSUE inside:  
-Procrastinator Editor Confesses: "I am, and have been for several months, a closet Homeowner? 
-Recurrent cultural nuisance Lagreco admits to illiteracy. "I find drugs very seducing." 
-Is empathy dead in America? Who cares') 

THE MUD ARE LURKING IN YOUR NEIGHBORHOOD! 
Sept 't 
Court Tavern 
I I pin Neu, Iiruihn lit 5.1 
Thu t 14 Lehigh University 8 • m Bethlehem PA (610) 758-4187 I pt IA Old City Hall 11111111 ()%m vim N1 LSI 51343-9453 'Sat Sept 16 East L.A. 10pm Sy newt NY (315) 471-1148 1 It Mt I Ludlow Street Cafe Ilpm 'St.)) 1, %) (212)353-D536 Fri Oct 13 Wet ands 1 New York NY (212) 966-4223 0,1 11 Rum Runners I1pm (.• m \ ISIS) 7$9.12911 Fri Nov 3 East L.A. lOpm Syracuse NY (31.5)471-1148 Sal Nos .1 Old City Hall 111pm thnem• 131:13.0.9453 Sat Nov 18 A.K.A. 1 1pm New York NY (212)673.7325 '-It Mother McGee's I Upon 11111111110.111 ‘1 1,11.1:+1.166'' 

1951 2nd Avenue. New York. NY 100221 
</article>
<article>
Twenty Reasons Why Bourbon is getter Than Peer 
1. All, told, it is cheaper 2. Less of your friends will want sore 3. Easier to smuggle into shows 4. Sweeter on the breath 6. Doesn't make you gaseous 6. Mixes with ginger ale 7. Can be drunk warm 8. Won't go flat 9. Gets you drunk easier 10. Hangover not as bad (compara-tively) 11. Less calories 
PROCRASTINATOR MILESTONES 
Engaged: Enrico Krappc, current Feature Writer of-the Procrastinator's sister publication "Sluggard". recently announced his engagement to perenially groggy social moth Conchisqua Jugo Naranja. The couple mct while vacationing at the luxurious Maison Du Fromage D'Oneil in balmy Secaucus. NJ late last Fall. A December wedding is planned. but sudden disenchantment and a bitter, unrequited breakup is expected. 

Still Steamed: Mud crony Dom Mottin still winces at the very mention of Conner flame and Internet Polyglot Lisa Loeb. The ill fated AOL romance, which smacks of a straight to video Billy Blanks movie, took place in my twisted mind early last December. "Several promises and sacri., A (ices were made. I quit my job. relined my conge4•5" with Aspergum and fed my roommate Hemornd for that woman", said the stung minstrel, slowly twist-ing a matted lock of hair. The sordid affair struck bottom when Mottin found out that he was actuallv conversing with local armchair pundit (and star of Fox's new sitcom "Enemies") ITHarem Beret, who was posing as Loeb for reasons unobtainable by phone Fed Up: Inchoate homeowner Max Veil and his stunning new wife Djongo are pretty damn sick of the infu-sion of bi-level haircuts on television. They led a chaotic two person demonstration on the Center for Embarrassing Social Trends in Washington. DC last Thursday. chanting '1 fear for your children, Mr. Pennishecd!" and hurling hot yogurt at nearby teenagers. Local police were busy elsewhere. 
12. Less filling Retiring: Procrastinator's long time corn-panion and janitor Rufus Kolapsin announced his 13. Ole bottle equals 21 bottles of plans to retire "Probably when I turn 50" last week. Rufus. who is now 14, was told, "Less Talk, Morc 
beer, hence easier to carry 
14. and less to clean up 16. and No Deposit 16. Tastes better 17. Separates the men from the boys 11. Separates the women from the girls 19. Unites the man with the women 20. Puts the girls and boys to sleep 
Scrubbing" by • ruthless editorial staff. Executed: Convicted Serial Killer Hans Moleman was executed by electric chair last month after I inner ate his last meal. ern:keared: Contributing writer and pseudo-lib-irk 1Cirstin• suffered a sprained ego atter a brief grapple with fate twenty years ago today, right after Sargent "Three-Toe" Feller taught the Klan to slay. Neither the fallen bourbon maven nor the inappropriately mentioned and extremely esoteric fictional character answered incessant cold calls, which prompted a swift return to reason 
Missing: Decent Writer Cecil y We met but briefly at the Cafe-a-Go-Go in late June. You told me the Procrastinator was filled with refreshingly dry wit. Won't you put it in writing? or anything else you write would be great, and guaranteed to be printed! Yours, Erich 
• Names Changed to prevent further catering to Steady insufferable attention 
madonna 

• 
SCOTT LEER TO LEAVE IgfD BAND!!! 
'If I had but two ryes to give to lehe mud, I would" amended the amed entertainer 'since I have but one, I am spend-ing it all on snacks." When • asked what kind of snacks, he would not reply Certainly, you readers as well as us editors are deeply sad-dened by the departure of the Mud's red-faced ultra funky it 
EDITOR'S NOTE: We actually received some !sedges from a stranger recently (I) Nalunaly 11 was negative. The issue concerned the Procraslriatoes condemnation of bety and eyebrow nngs(2/95) flowerer. our Moment was not passed arbitrarily. According to the 'American Journal at Nursing' (5/94), 94% of all belly and eyebrow piercing& end in infection and subsequent removal So don't think that we are growaig caws:thus or conservative I think bekyrings are •coot, but I personally witnessed a friend's pain and &utterly for months before she got hem removed. leaving pertnanent scar tissue and a hehefty non-Insurable prescription to antiblolcs MM 
Page 2 

frontman. The Mud themselves will deeply feel their their loss as their van ride banter will no longer be as full of zingy repartees. Most of all, Don Martin will be out of an opponent/con-federate in the eternal battle of cheeky one-lin-ers that fills up the Mud's quieter moments. We wish Scott well in his new career direc-tions. Among them are plans for a solo album, curbside street preach-ing and a series of edu-cational video tapes on the art of ego massage. Procrastinator • July. 1995 
</article>
<article>
X MARKS THE JONESER 
Know your tonesco He is everywhere He is reading this over your shoulder right now because he rs too cheap to buy his own, even though the is free. Know him Know the feel of his breath on the nape of your neck He (or she) is the one •,.....arderramding. asking all the tine. WII you get me high? while they don't have any of thee own Thee appetite exceeds yours, but you have a bag, and they don't. They end up smolong more of yours than you do Is this lair? No. but the toneset doesn't think in this way. Know your jonosol When the poneser arrives at your apartment they are empty-handed. but soon they have found plenty of beers. on YOUR fudge. When the hal is passed around for a case, the joneser laments they Reveal gone to the bank machine. that they 'aren't in the mood to drink anymore" though you know the mood wil pass with the amval of a cold case of Bass The ponerser then asks if 4 is okay to smoke. You grudgingly elm it, but it then turns out that they have no cig-aretles and Jones one off of you You have depleted your pocket supply and are forced to deplete your emergency stash. Know your prosier. 
Why? You may wonder. Since there a nothing you can do You cannot confront a sinew about his pnesing The presser is too clever, too cunning They wet whop the words back at you and all the real of the crowd we thank you are 'stingy' So just be knoweig the joneser knows that you know that they are a jocose( You are onto them. and the tine we come soon that vengeance is thme In the meantime. hide the beers in the crisper, break your bag down into tiny stashes so you can make a pant of how See you have left. And most impenitent stop smoking all together 
This has been a peel public service announcement for FUJ. the Federation to Undermine Jonosers. Send all donations to Box 309. Hey Pocky Way. Lonesome:man. NJ 08807 
ARE YOU DRUM? A Handy Test 
1 If you had another dnnk nght now you would be a. Ready to dare home b. Ready to vomit c. Starling to slur d. Completely incoherent 
2. The Klee of gong Snny-dipping in Lake Ontario sounds: a. Insane b. foolhardy c. necessary d. boring 
3. Whet word more closely descries You new: 
a Bnliant b Obnoxious c Sullen 
4 II someone gave you a percodan right now you would a Grudgingly decent b Saves for tomorrow c Take it and throw up d. Take it and pass out e. Take it and go out 
SCORING: 1)A.-SponleA3-2/C-113- 3.:21A-018-1C.3005:3)A-443-3/C-243- 5:4)A-1/13-0/C-5.13-4/E-10 
1-5 You are only buzzed, have a few more drinks and wart for your second wind 6.10 You are doing fine just take I easy and don't let them gyre you arty more Jaegermender 11-20 Time to have a glass of water and f figure out who's dirang your home 
LRAM W1111 LUYT 
Especially here in New York City, a simple walk down the street in summer can turn your once obedient body into a surge of raging lustful pheromone phenomena. A gorgeous model walks by in a skin Ight. low an summer frock and guys and girls practically buckle over in longing and animal desire. Old. steady relationships are put to the test and single guys seriously debate suicide, as an almost insurmountable frustration of sexual desire pervades the at. 
How can you cope with all this lovely. exposed, sun and smog ripened flesh? You want to own al, fen a and touch l and kiss it so badly that even to have just one wouldn't be near enough. .1 you owl sleep with every woman who walks by. life just Mil worth hving and you start to ay '''•-•*dilow can you Iran your eyes not to ravage every loon you find appealing? The poor women walk around feeling Ike pieces of meat in a starving Inn's don Meanwhile. sound and reward-ing relationships are put Into jeopardy by the endless sea of promising faces. tethere can you lum? Certainly not to the Lord Turn to your heart. know these women are all sinners. whores and scar-mongers (don't ask me what that means) and know that the ells woman whO Is Vaal-:1g for you just when you come home at night, is all you realty need. Yes, that little woman. How tal is she now? Just keep watering her and waiting and soon she we be big enough to take out with you! Oh God, 1 cannot wad to go home and get drunk. alone. In front of the televi-sion! NI the way horns I will wear blinders so that I do not soo the sea of beautiful women, and I wit be free...FREE, 
MAX'S ONE-SHOT IDCR$ QUIZ 1. Aftlent teepee the charts in 1983 with the cloying but catchy syrup ballad 'Harden My Heart' An opportunistic agent and a fickle public left this tong Pat Sonata! ensemble out in the cold. 
2 Their name fist came from the bubblegum music of the *arty sev-enties. They had a brief moment of stardom with their hit 'Willy Won't Go Home' on 1972. then laded away Ste so many Osmonds and Archies 
3. He m, he had fun, but only one season in the sun in 1978. A bitter divorce matched with stiff California reciprocity laws left this bal-!edit dangling by he 1040s. 
4. They used the public's fascina-tion with gangsters as a spring-board to stardom with their 1975 hit The Night Chicago Died-Unfortunately. there were one too many sender sounding and lookng bands for them to keep thew heads above water. 
5. This sear! wearing Scottish group had a 1977 hit entitled 'Magic', until other falsetto voiced power groups like Yes, Styx and Supertramp edged this feeble clone out of the picture. along with April Milne and Asia. 6. Arguably the most memorable phone number in history (aside from 970-FIST). '867-5309' caught the MTV wave in 1981 and brought this "Johnny Two-note' a brief lecher of stardom. 
•UALPOI '9 Kid '9 eori ;faded 
scar C lamS Wi49olnin0 

CAPSULE CWILM ft 3.•r Mar_VMWS 
FILM 
The Bridges or Lathan' County (Starring Clont Eastwood and Bruce WIts) 
A tepid yawner in which elements of the Die Hard films co-mingle with country bumpkin soap opera. Detective Rory Calhoun (Willis) plays a drifting. alcoholic NYPD defective who. after getting lost on has way to a drunk driving rally. manages to fall desperately in love with a local sheriff (tenderly Oared by Clue Eastwood) who teaches him skeet shooting and rodeo riding (with a Willis One hilarious horse get-up') Their banal buddy-buddy bonding is enhanced by a couple of songs (if you can believe it, Chit sings even better than he did in Paint Your Wagon) and a neat fanta-sy interlude. Nevertheless, the is hackneyed stuff we've seen before (Kurt and Sty led it better In Los! Tango in Tango 6 Cash) C 
Species (Sleeker Rory Calhoun. Jeff Bridges) 
Jeff 8ndges overacts horrendously in thus glum turkey about a run-amok alien (played by Calhoun on a hellbent!), understated costume) who attempts to splice has genes with those of Calvin Klein. In the ensuing fashion holocaust, replete with a 
cameo by a demented Gloria Vanderbilt. we lose something on the feel for the char-acters. Obviously this is just to play for the lawyers for Bridges, whose delusional lawsuit against the 'neater* of 'Budges of DieHard County" os Sol boring viewers on CNN Wart for the video. Da 
(B001.XS 
Teeth Like an Olive by John Grisham (Mangled Press. 345 pgs hardcover 54.99) 
In a startling new direction. acclaimed mega-success John Grisham takes leave backwoods lawyer intrigue to bring us the laconic tale of a dissatisfied slacker sou-Pe (astoundingly played astoundingly nothing more than a string of words on paper) who invest In a small olive grove. Complications arose when the thirsty older brother appears out of nowhere with a huge vat of gin and some dry vermouth Grisham uses his standard methods of slowly building the unrelentng suspense as the awe supply starts to mysteriously dwindle. Is the brother responsible or is 4 something far more sinister? After 300 pages. you wont care either. Be 
Wacker by Stephen King (Knopf 6 Handler. 2.635 pgs, $4.99) 
It seems Stephen King will never tire of tales about household appliances run amok. Henry. • garden ranee, weed wacker absorbs the soul of a rabid squirts t scooter. tally decapitates. Soon, the weedwacker is developing a We of its own, pursuing car-rots and taking revenge on a John Deere mower (Ray Calhoun, in a bnIlianth understated performance) Al over 2,000 pages, one wonders d Mr. King should get out of the house once on • whole. Surety carpal tunnel syndrome is Eminent In the meantime, Kng fans should have no complaints. A 
Procrastinator • July. 1995 
Page 3 
</article>
<article>
ALCOHOL: MAN'S MUCH MALIGNED MASTER 
(or %I'm not a drunkard just because ci drink more than Tout) 
Alcohol is a leromous power. a simultaneous curse and a saviour can turn a mouse Into a lion, A can lum a min into a drooling idiot, it can kit, it can cure can make ugly seem beautiful, relax muscles ease grist and suffenng. stimulate conversation and good will. It can fog the memory of last night while also making Iasi night memorable. II is poetic justice. a terrible cute a deal with the devil. a mood° and it must not be blamed for the frailties and weaknesses of its users. Alcohol has been accused of everything from hampering motor skills to causing war and 'health emblems". Well. this may tie so, but don't let them say thA alt.ohe I ;:oesn't troy funrier mute lik-able, or more popular. The nay-sayers argument is 'He isn't malty funnier or more likable when he's thinking he just thinks he is? 
But isn't thinking you are popular really what Ns all about? They might say lie only thinks he has sen-confdence.' an 'reedy absurd statement. II you make People laugh. you are funny. but the poo-pooers of alC0h01 will disagree. They will say people are laugh inp at you. not with you, or they will say that their laughter is a sublimation of pity or concern. They are foolish to say these things, yet nobody laughs at them ever 01 course, if you're sober. drinkers can be annoying then breath is overwhelming and they are loud, even obnoxious. But lake a drink yoursal 
and all Moe annoying trails vanish. So where do you draw the line? If alcohol makes you feel loved and varm and comfy, why not stay drunk all the time? What does the physical deterioration, cold sweats. shakes and deleium liniment matter? Maybe you can sidestep these ail mends by drinking only on the weekends. ca Ismiling yow weekly drinks. or not drink-mg bracers 400 pm Even then. some pamphlet somewhere will tell you that you re a *emblem' drinker. sooner or late'. they might In tight But are you Or is society just trying to bring you down? Are you being punished Lecause a bunch of other folks can't handle their liquor; 
-sidArack One America. Lane of Addiction Our society itself ix hopelessly addicted—not just to alcohol but to addiction itself Once 21, a freshly legal drinker still has no counsel in the development of niudtate habits. The French children have wino met dinner all through chaMond, teaming from the beginning to "go easy' lest they embairass themselves at Ina dinner lobe. The American child is forbidden to drink at all Only after his parents are gone to bed does hn 12ICI the liquor cabinet, drink too much and wind up n the hospital el, t, alcohol education is a concerned dodoes An. pamphlet Before he "yen mashes the legal drinking age, he is pronounced an alcohokc. 

The more we tell the child to 'just say no". the mow seductive and intriguing 'yes becomes The child yews up behoving he has no self-conlrol, and so must say "f10+ to everything instead ol 'Okay, just one In America there is no such thing as 'lust one- whether it be potato clops. cigarettes. sexual partners or Imes of cocaine. A snot of whiskey leads straight to alcoholism and then rehab. where Clockwork Orangeesque behavioral modi-fication techniques seen make one vomit at the taste of alcohol. We leave rehab 'cum' but she governed by an addictive personality. only the revulsion and lea" of possible 'relapse outweighs our eternal thirst. This ex called "successful treatment yet one still has not !earned the first thing about see-conliol. becoming instead a rehab addict' attending AA meeting twcedaiy. driving the family crazy with pious lectures about the evils of drink. al the while refusing to believe alcohol is completely innocent. that the power that causes NO much non Isola Own weakness, and selfishness. 
In conclusion. the lock to living a full life with alcohol is knowing hew to pace yourself. By steeling your reason against the liquid abyss, you can have a op-marine geed time every weekend. 
MUM mourn THE 11•LITICALLY /PATHETIC 
It Is a eel known fact that Packers are much loo con• Cerned with work shirking and authority evasion to be bothered with such trivialities as health and wealth. Subsequent consume' goods have developed to sue the demands of this abberant culture, products which cater to the mittant-gratification-lakes-too-long maid-set. 
PATENT810973498EU 'Piton's Bucket of Worms" EA. Retail $19.95 This product Offers all the comforts Of Mortal without the hangover Feel the mescaline pulse through your veins as you munch a handful of those babies. Perfect for family picnics, sporting events, bar snacks. 

or lust relaxing in front of the TV And you think your kids fight over the remote! 
PATENTI1472378490389WJI 'Mad Donna's Suet Cubes' Eat Retail $4.95 
Anyone who had patriotic parents will enjoy mammies of 4th of July picnics. fire-crackers. hot dogs. corn on the cob and Mom's baked beans. Now you can enjoy those succulent cubes of let that came in the bean jar oy !no bowlful! Delicious with warm Budweiser 

PATENTS53289982390AJIS 'Mickey Finn's Gallon O'Brine' Est. Retail: $14.99 
Like pickles? Like pick-led eggs? Pickled beefs? Pickled kidneys and shrunken lovers? When the pickle jar is empty do you fight tooth and nail over the remaining pickle juice? Do you savor the salty broth with blissful pas-sion? Before seeking extensive therapy. try some of Mickey's hcme-made pickling bone. its warm. A's sour, and best of all. d can lead to high Wad pressure!! 

EVERY MOWER'S 14TOMMTARE 

Papa 4 
Tow p 44- .4% ete'sa Si j 5.0 ^al ralirsikes:. 
re—

(pA rtil re let sows kit'. I'M 1001- ,  ti 

Procrastinator • July, 1995 
</article>
</articles>